<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<STIGComments Name="XO_ASD">
  
  <Vuln ID="V-222387">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222388">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222389">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: Non-privileged user sessions must time out after 15 minutes of inactivity (APSC-DV-000070).

Xen Orchestra does not natively expose a configurable idle session timeout in config.toml or via environment variable.
The check searched config.toml, process environment, and XO source for sessionTimeout, idleTimeout, or token
expiration settings. No qualifying 15-minute inactivity timeout was detected.

Remediation options:
1. Configure a reverse proxy (nginx) in front of XO to enforce session idle timeouts using proxy_read_timeout
   and proxy_send_timeout directives set to 900 seconds (15 minutes).
2. Implement network-level session enforcement via firewall idle-connection timeout rules.
3. Contact Vates to request a configurable session idle timeout feature in a future XO release.
4. Document a compensating control accepted by the AO if a technical solution is not feasible.

Reference: The AO must accept this finding or document a compensating control in the SSP.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222390">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: Administrator sessions must time out after 10 minutes of inactivity (APSC-DV-000080).

Xen Orchestra applies a single session expiration policy to all users and does not differentiate between
administrator and non-privileged user sessions. The check found no per-role idle timeout configuration
in config.toml, process environment, or source. The 10-minute administrator timeout requirement cannot
be enforced through native XO configuration.

Remediation options:
1. Implement differentiated timeout enforcement via a reverse proxy (nginx) or load balancer that
   applies shorter session timeouts to administrative URL paths (e.g., /api/admin/*).
2. Configure administrative access through a privileged access workstation (PAW) or jump server
   that enforces 10-minute idle lockouts at the OS level.
3. Contact Vates to request role-based session timeout support in a future XO release.
4. Document this as an accepted risk with compensating controls in the SSP.

Reference: APSC-DV-000080. The AO must accept this finding or document a compensating control.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222391">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: The application must provide a user-initiated logoff capability (APSC-DV-000090).

Xen Orchestra provides a built-in logoff capability through multiple mechanisms:
- Web UI: Sign Out button accessible from the user menu in the top navigation bar terminates the session.
- REST API: The /rest/v0/sessions/current endpoint accepts DELETE requests to invalidate the current session.
- XO CLI: The xo-cli session.signOut command terminates the authenticated session programmatically.

Session termination is confirmed by verifying that authenticated API requests return HTTP 401 after logout.
XO uses server-side session tokens stored in LevelDB; logout invalidates the token server-side, preventing reuse.

This finding is Not A Finding. Xen Orchestra fully satisfies the logoff capability requirement.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: The application must provide a user-initiated logoff capability (APSC-DV-000090).

The automated check could not confirm XO's logout capability on this system. Possible causes:
- XO process is not running or is not accessible on port 443.
- The REST API endpoint /rest/v0/sessions/current is not responding.
- XO is deployed behind a proxy that is filtering the check.

Manual verification steps:
1. Log in to the Xen Orchestra web interface.
2. Confirm a Sign Out or Logout option is present in the user menu.
3. Click Sign Out and verify you are redirected to the login page.
4. Attempt to access a protected resource after logout and confirm HTTP 401 is returned.

If manual verification confirms logout works, document the evidence and mark as NotAFinding in the CKL.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222392">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: The application must display an explicit logoff message confirming session termination (APSC-DV-000100, CAT III).

The automated check searched the xo-web compiled JavaScript distribution for explicit session-terminated
confirmation messages (e.g., "You have been logged out", "Session terminated"). While XO redirects users
to the login page after logout, no explicit confirmation message text was detected in the source.

Manual verification steps:
1. Log in to the Xen Orchestra web interface.
2. Click Sign Out from the user menu.
3. Observe whether the application displays a message such as "You have been signed out" or "Session terminated
   successfully" before or after redirecting to the login page.
4. If such a message is displayed, document it with a screenshot and mark as NotAFinding.
5. If no message is displayed (only a redirect to login), this remains an Open finding.

Remediation: Request Vates add an explicit logout confirmation message to the XO web interface.
This is a CAT III (low severity) finding. Document as accepted risk if remediation is not feasible.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222393">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
Not Applicable: Xen Orchestra is a hypervisor management platform that manages VMs, hosts, and storage.
It does not store or process classified, CUI, or user-defined data objects requiring security attribute
labeling (e.g., classification markings). The STIG requires security attribute association only for
applications that store data subject to mandatory access control (MAC) or sensitivity labeling policies.
XO stores infrastructure configuration data (VM configs, user credentials, audit logs), not mission data.
This requirement does not apply to infrastructure management software of this type.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222394">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
Not Applicable: Xen Orchestra does not process classified, CUI, or sensitivity-labeled data objects
requiring in-process security attribute association. XO processes infrastructure management data
(API requests, VM operations, host metrics) that does not carry data classification markings.
This STIG control applies to applications that process data subject to mandatory access control (MAC)
policies where security attributes (classification, sensitivity labels) must be tracked through
processing pipelines. XO is an infrastructure management tool, not a data processing application
subject to data labeling requirements. This requirement does not apply.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222395">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
Not Applicable: Xen Orchestra does not transmit classified, CUI, or sensitivity-labeled data objects
requiring security attribute association during transmission. XO transmits infrastructure management
data (API responses, VM state, metrics) over TLS-protected channels, but this data does not carry
mandatory access control (MAC) classification labels that must travel with the data.

TLS confidentiality and integrity protection for XO API transmissions is covered separately by
V-222396 (confidentiality) and V-222397 (integrity). This control specifically requires applications
to embed and preserve data classification attributes (e.g., FOUO, SECRET) in transmitted messages.
As an infrastructure management tool, XO does not handle data subject to this labeling requirement.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222396">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: DoD-approved encryption (TLS 1.2 or higher) must protect all remote access sessions (APSC-DV-000160).

The automated check confirmed that Xen Orchestra accepts TLS 1.2 and/or TLS 1.3 connections on port 443,
and TLS 1.0 (weak protocol) is disabled. This satisfies the DoD requirement for FIPS 140-2 approved
encryption protecting session confidentiality.

TLS 1.2 and TLS 1.3 use AES-based cipher suites which are FIPS 140-2 approved. TLS 1.0 is disabled,
eliminating known weaknesses (e.g., POODLE, BEAST). All XO API and web UI traffic is encrypted end-to-end.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: DoD-approved encryption (TLS 1.2 or higher) must protect all remote access sessions (APSC-DV-000160).

The automated check detected one of the following conditions:
- TLS 1.2 and TLS 1.3 are not active on port 443 (TLS not configured or not accessible).
- TLS 1.0 is active alongside TLS 1.2/1.3 (weak protocol must be disabled).

Remediation steps:
1. Verify XO is listening on port 443: ss -tlnp | grep :443
2. Review config.toml for TLS certificate configuration (bindAddress, certificate, key fields).
3. Disable TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 in the Node.js TLS configuration using --tls-min-v1.2 flag
   or by setting minVersion: 'TLSv1.2' in the https.createServer options.
4. Restart the xo-server service: systemctl restart xo-server
5. Verify with: echo Q | openssl s_client -connect HOSTNAME:443 -tls1_2 2&gt;&amp;1 | grep "Cipher is"
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222397">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: Cryptographic mechanisms must protect the integrity of all remote access sessions (APSC-DV-000170).

The automated check confirmed that Xen Orchestra accepts TLS 1.2 and/or TLS 1.3 connections on port 443,
and TLS 1.0 (which lacks adequate integrity protection) is disabled.

TLS 1.2 and TLS 1.3 use HMAC-based message authentication (e.g., HMAC-SHA256 in TLS 1.2, AEAD in TLS 1.3)
to ensure integrity of all transmitted data. Any in-transit modification of encrypted TLS records is
detected and the connection is terminated. This satisfies the DoD requirement for cryptographic integrity
protection of remote access sessions.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
STIG Requirement: Cryptographic mechanisms must protect the integrity of all remote access sessions (APSC-DV-000170).

The automated check detected one of the following conditions:
- TLS 1.2 and TLS 1.3 are not active on port 443.
- TLS 1.0 is active (does not provide adequate integrity protection and must be disabled).

Remediation steps:
1. Verify XO is listening on port 443: ss -tlnp | grep :443
2. Review config.toml for TLS certificate and key configuration.
3. Enforce minimum TLS 1.2 by adding --tls-min-v1.2 to xo-server startup parameters
   or setting minVersion: 'TLSv1.2' in Node.js https.createServer options.
4. Disable TLS 1.0 and TLS 1.1 explicitly.
5. Restart the xo-server service: systemctl restart xo-server
6. Re-test TLS configuration after restart.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222398">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
Not Applicable: Xen Orchestra does not use SOAP (Simple Object Access Protocol) for any of its interfaces.

XO exposes a REST/JSON API over HTTPS and a WebSocket JSON-RPC interface. Both are modern protocols
that do not use XML-based SOAP messaging. Node.js/Express.js applications do not natively support SOAP.
No SOAP, WSDL, or XML-RPC references were detected in the XO source code.

The STIG requirement applies only to applications that use SOAP messaging. Since XO does not use SOAP,
this control does not apply. TLS-based integrity for XO's REST and WebSocket interfaces is covered
by V-222397. This finding is Not Applicable.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>
The automated check detected potential SOAP, WSDL, or XML-RPC references in the Xen Orchestra source code.

Manual verification required:
1. Review the detected references to determine if they represent active SOAP endpoints or merely
   code comments, documentation, or library imports.
2. If active SOAP messaging is confirmed, verify that all SOAP messages include:
   - Message ID
   - Service Request element
   - Timestamp element
   - SAML Assertion (if applicable)
   - Digital signatures on all message elements
3. If no active SOAP endpoints are found, update the finding to Not_Applicable with supporting evidence.

If SOAP is confirmed but not properly secured, contact Vates to implement WS-Security digital signing.
        </ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222399">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222400">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222401">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no active SAML configuration in XO config files (/opt/xo/xo-server/config.toml or /etc/xo-server/config.toml). XO supports SAML via the @xen-orchestra/auth-saml plugin, but SAML is not enabled on this system. This control requires SAML authentication to be configured and active; since SAML is not in use, the control is Not Applicable.

If SAML is later enabled, this finding must be re-evaluated. The SAML IdP must generate a unique assertion ID (the saml:Assertion ID attribute) for every assertion it issues. Verify the IdP configuration enforces uniqueness — most modern IdPs (ADFS, Okta, Azure AD) do this by default.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected active SAML configuration in XO config.toml. XO delegates SAML assertion handling to the configured Identity Provider (IdP). This control requires the ISSO/ISSM to verify with the IdP administrator that:

1. The IdP generates a unique ID attribute for every SAML assertion issued to XO.
2. The XO SAML plugin does not accept assertions with duplicate or reused IDs.
3. The IdP enforces the uniqueness requirement per SAML 2.0 Core section 1.3.4.

Action required: Obtain documentation or configuration evidence from the IdP administrator confirming assertion ID uniqueness is enforced. Document the IdP product, version, and the uniqueness enforcement mechanism (e.g., ADFS enforces this by default via the AssertionID attribute generated as a GUID).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222402">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan confirmed XO (Xen Orchestra) uses a REST/JSON API architecture, not SOAP/WS-Security. WS-Security encrypted assertion tokens are a SOAP-specific mechanism (WS-Security standard, OASIS 2004). XO has no SOAP endpoint, no WS-Security middleware, and no assertion intermediary in the SOAP sense.

XO API communications occur over HTTPS (TLS), which provides equivalent confidentiality protection for all data in transit. Authentication uses JSON Web Token (JWT) session tokens issued over TLS, not SOAP assertion tokens passed through XML intermediaries. This control is Not Applicable because the technology (WS-Security/SOAP assertions) is not used by XO.

Note: If a future XO deployment introduces a SOAP-based integration gateway, this finding must be re-evaluated for that component.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222403">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222404">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222405">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no active SAML configuration on this system. The OneTimeUse element is a SAML 2.0 Conditions element restriction that prevents assertion replay. Since SAML is not configured, no SAML assertions are generated and this control does not apply.

If SAML is later enabled, verify: (1) the IdP only includes at most one OneTimeUse element per assertion Conditions block; (2) the XO SAML plugin enforces single-use assertion consumption and rejects replays. Most SAML 2.0-compliant IdPs enforce this automatically.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected active SAML configuration. SAML 2.0 Core (section 2.5.1.5) requires that the Conditions element contain at most one OneTimeUse element per assertion. XO delegates SAML assertion processing to the @xen-orchestra/auth-saml plugin and the upstream IdP.

Action required: The ISSO/ISSM must verify with the IdP administrator that:
1. The IdP never includes more than one OneTimeUse element in the Conditions block of any assertion sent to XO.
2. The XO SAML plugin enforces OneTimeUse semantics — each assertion is only accepted once (replay protection).

Document the IdP product, version, and the configuration or code reference confirming OneTimeUse enforcement. Common IdPs (ADFS, Okta, Azure AD) enforce this by default and may be documented by citing the product compliance statement.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222406">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no active SAML configuration on this system. The SessionIndex attribute is a SAML 2.0 element used in AuthnStatement to correlate the IdP session with the SP session. Since SAML is not configured, no SAML SessionIndex values are generated or transmitted, and this control does not apply.

If SAML is later enabled, verify: (1) all SAML messages containing a SessionIndex attribute are transmitted over encrypted channels (HTTPS/TLS); (2) the XO SAML plugin is configured to reject unencrypted SAML responses. XO's TLS-only API configuration provides this protection by default.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected active SAML configuration. SAML 2.0 SessionIndex values that are correlated with user privacy data must be transmitted only over encrypted channels.

Action required: The ISSO/ISSM must verify:
1. All SAML AuthnResponse and LogoutRequest messages containing SessionIndex are sent only over HTTPS (TLS 1.2 or higher).
2. The XO application does not accept SAML messages over plain HTTP.
3. The IdP is configured to only deliver assertions to the registered HTTPS Assertion Consumer Service (ACS) URL.

Verify the ACS URL registered in the IdP for XO uses https:// not http://. Document the IdP configuration and confirm TLS is enforced end-to-end between IdP and XO. XO's default TLS configuration (if properly configured) satisfies this requirement.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222407">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected LDAP or Active Directory integration configured in XO config.toml. LDAP/AD integration satisfies the requirement for automated account management mechanisms by delegating user provisioning, disabling, and removal to the enterprise directory service.

This means: (1) when a user account is disabled or deleted in Active Directory, XO authentication fails automatically at the next login attempt; (2) account creation, modification, and termination workflows are handled by the enterprise IdM/IdP system (e.g., AD, LDAP); (3) XO local account management is supplemented by the directory service's automated account lifecycle controls.

The ISSO/ISSM should document the LDAP/AD integration as the automated account management mechanism in the system's authorization artifacts.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no LDAP or Active Directory integration in XO config files. XO is operating with local account management only, which requires manual administrative action for each account lifecycle event.

Action required to achieve compliance:
1. Configure LDAP/AD integration in XO config.toml under the [ldap] section (or equivalent SAML/OIDC integration).
2. Alternatively, integrate XO with an enterprise Identity Management (IdM) system that provides automated provisioning/deprovisioning via SCIM or LDAP.

Without automated account management, the ISSO/ISSM must document a compensating control: a manual account review process with a defined schedule (recommend monthly) and documented evidence of reviews. This compensating control must be approved in the ATO package.

Reference: config.toml LDAP configuration requires: ldap.url, ldap.bindDn, ldap.bindPassword, ldap.filter, and ldap.base entries.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222408">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222409">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan confirmed XO does not have a native mechanism to automatically expire or disable temporary accounts after 72 hours. XO account management is primarily through the web UI or xo-cli; there is no built-in account expiry field or scheduled deprovisioning job.

Action required (choose one):
1. LDAP/AD integration: Configure temporary accounts in Active Directory with an account expiration set to 72 hours from creation. XO will inherit the AD account expiry automatically.
2. Administrative procedure: Implement a documented manual process where administrators create temporary accounts and schedule removal within 72 hours. The process must include: (a) a creation log with timestamp, (b) a scheduled reminder or ticket, (c) evidence of removal/disabling within 72 hours.
3. External automation: Use the XO REST API (/rest/v0/users) with a scheduled job (cron/systemd timer) to disable or remove accounts created more than 72 hours ago.

Document the chosen approach in the ISSO/ISSM authorization artifacts. If no temporary accounts are ever provisioned on this system, document that policy as a compensating control.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222410">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no emergency account designation or protection mechanism in XO. XO does not implement a concept of "emergency accounts" (also called break-glass or PACE accounts) as a distinct account type with protected status. All XO administrator accounts have equal administrative rights and can be enabled or disabled by any other administrator.

Emergency access to the underlying XO infrastructure is handled at the operating system level (Debian 12 root account, SSH key-based access) rather than within the XO application itself. The operating system emergency access controls are assessed separately under the GPOS SRG for Debian 12.

Since XO has no application-level emergency account feature or account type distinction, this control is Not Applicable. Document this assessment in the authorization artifacts noting that emergency system access relies on OS-level administrative mechanisms.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222411">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no native inactivity-based account disable mechanism in XO. XO does not track last-login timestamps for accounts or automatically disable accounts after a period of inactivity. The XO LevelDB database stores user credentials but does not implement inactivity enforcement.

Action required (choose one):
1. LDAP/AD integration: Configure Active Directory with the "Account is disabled after N days of inactivity" Group Policy Object (GPO). Set the threshold to 35 days. AD will disable accounts automatically; XO inherits this via LDAP authentication failure.
2. Administrative procedure: Implement a documented manual process where administrators review XO audit logs (or the XO user list via xo-cli) monthly and disable accounts with no login activity in the past 35 days. Document evidence of reviews.
3. External automation: Use the XO REST API (/rest/v0/users) with a scheduled job that compares user last-activity timestamps from audit logs against the 35-day threshold.

Document the chosen approach in the ISSO/ISSM authorization artifacts with evidence that inactivity monitoring is active and enforced.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222412">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan enumerated XO user accounts from the LevelDB database or XO REST API. The scan cannot automatically determine which accounts are "unnecessary" — this requires human judgment based on current organizational roles and responsibilities.

Action required:
1. Review the list of XO user accounts displayed in the Finding Details section.
2. For each account, verify that the account holder: (a) is a current employee or contractor, (b) still requires access to XO for their job function, (c) has the minimum required role (no excessive permissions).
3. Disable or delete any accounts for: former employees, transferred personnel no longer needing access, test/demo accounts, shared accounts with no current business justification, or service accounts for decommissioned integrations.
4. Document the account review with: reviewer name, date, accounts reviewed, actions taken, and justification for retained accounts.

Schedule periodic account reviews (recommend every 30 days) and maintain documentation as evidence for ATO compliance. Use "xo-cli --list-users" or the XO web UI (Settings &gt; Users) to perform the review.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222413">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured and no account creation events in the systemd
journal for the last 7 days. This is expected on systems where no account changes have been made recently.

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO/ISSM must verify one of the following:
1. Enable the XO audit plugin (xo-server-audit) which records all API operations including user.create events
2. Confirm XO audit logs are being forwarded to a SIEM that captures account creation events
3. Manually create a test account and verify the event is logged in the system journal or audit log

To enable the XO audit plugin: navigate to Settings &gt; Plugins in the XO web interface and enable xo-server-audit.
Once enabled, all user management actions are logged to the XO audit log and accessible via the REST API at
/rest/v0/plugins/audit/records.

If using LDAP/AD for account management, configure the auth-ldap plugin to satisfy this as Not Applicable.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is installed and configured. Account management
is delegated to the enterprise LDAP/AD directory service, which maintains its own comprehensive audit trail of
all account lifecycle events including creation.

ISSO must verify: Active Directory audit policy (Account Management category) is enabled and logs are retained
per DoD policy (minimum 1 year online, 3 years archived). AD account creation events appear as Event ID 4720
in the Windows Security Event Log.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found account creation events in the systemd journal. XO is logging account
creation activity as required by this control.

ISSO should verify: The XO audit plugin (xo-server-audit) is enabled and logs include account name and timestamp
at minimum. Audit logs should be retained per DoD requirements and forwarded to a centralized audit server.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222414">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured and no account modification events in the
systemd journal for the last 7 days.

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO/ISSM must verify one of the following:
1. Enable the XO audit plugin (xo-server-audit) to capture user.set events (account modifications)
2. Confirm XO audit logs are forwarded to a SIEM that captures account modification events
3. Manually modify a test account and verify the event appears in the audit log

XO account modification events via the audit plugin include role changes, password changes, and permission updates.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account management is delegated to
enterprise LDAP/AD, which maintains its own audit trail. Account modification events in AD appear as Event ID 4738
(user account changed) in the Windows Security Event Log.

ISSO must verify AD audit policy covers account management changes and logs are retained per DoD policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found account modification events in the systemd journal. XO is logging account
modification activity as required. ISSO should verify audit log retention and centralized forwarding.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222415">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured and no account disabling events in the
systemd journal for the last 7 days.

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO/ISSM must verify:
1. Enable the XO audit plugin (xo-server-audit) to capture account disable events
2. Confirm audit logs are forwarded to a centralized SIEM
3. Test by disabling a non-production account and verifying the event is logged

Note: XO does not have a native "disable account" feature separate from deletion. Accounts may be disabled by
removing permissions or by the LDAP/AD directory if configured.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account disabling is managed by
enterprise LDAP/AD. Account disable events in AD appear as Event ID 4725 (user account disabled).

ISSO must verify AD audit policy is enabled and logs retained per DoD policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found account disabling events in the systemd journal. XO is logging account
disabling activity as required. ISSO should verify audit log retention and centralized forwarding.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222416">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured and no account removal events in the
systemd journal for the last 7 days.

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO/ISSM must verify:
1. Enable the XO audit plugin (xo-server-audit) to capture user deletion events
2. Confirm audit logs are forwarded to a centralized SIEM
3. Test by deleting a non-production account and verifying the event is logged

Account deletion in XO is logged as a user.delete action in the audit log when the audit plugin is enabled.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account removal is managed by
enterprise LDAP/AD. Account deletion events in AD appear as Event ID 4726 (user account deleted).

ISSO must verify AD audit policy is enabled and logs retained per DoD policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found account removal events in the systemd journal. XO is logging account
removal activity as required. ISSO should verify audit log retention and centralized forwarding.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222417">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured. XO does not natively send notifications
to SAs/ISSOs when accounts are created.

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO/ISSM must implement a compensating control:
Option 1 (SIEM): Configure SIEM to alert SA/ISSO when XO audit log records a user.create event
Option 2 (ITSM): Require all account creation requests to go through a ticketing system (ServiceNow, Jira) that
  automatically notifies SA/ISSO via email/ticket assignment
Option 3 (Script): Deploy a monitoring script that polls the XO API /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records and sends
  email alerts when new user.create events are detected

Document the implemented compensating control in the System Security Plan.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account creation notifications
to SA/ISSO are handled by the enterprise LDAP/AD directory service processes and procedures.

ISSO must verify the enterprise AD account management process includes SA/ISSO notification on account creation
per DoD account management procedures.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222418">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured. XO does not natively notify SA/ISSO
when accounts are modified.

ACTION REQUIRED - Implement a compensating control:
Option 1: Configure SIEM to alert on user.set events from XO audit log
Option 2: Require account modification requests through an ITSM system with automatic SA/ISSO notification
Option 3: Deploy monitoring script polling XO API for account modification events

Significant account modifications include: role changes, permission updates, password resets, and group membership
changes. All of these are captured by the XO audit plugin when enabled.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account modification notifications
are handled by enterprise LDAP/AD directory service procedures. ISSO must verify the AD account management process
includes SA/ISSO notification on account changes.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222419">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured. XO does not natively notify SA/ISSO
when accounts are disabled.

ACTION REQUIRED - Implement a compensating control for account disable notifications:
Option 1: Configure SIEM to alert SA/ISSO when XO audit log records an account disable event
Option 2: Require account disable requests through ITSM with automatic SA/ISSO notification workflow
Option 3: Establish manual procedure where any XO account disablement triggers immediate SA/ISSO email notification

Document the implemented procedure in the System Security Plan and ensure it is tested annually.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account disabling notifications
are handled by enterprise LDAP/AD procedures. ISSO must verify AD procedures include SA/ISSO notification on
account disabling per DoD account management policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222420">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured. XO does not natively notify SA/ISSO
when accounts are removed.

ACTION REQUIRED - Implement a compensating control for account removal notifications:
Option 1: Configure SIEM to alert SA/ISSO when XO audit log records a user.delete event
Option 2: Require account removal requests through ITSM with automatic SA/ISSO notification
Option 3: Establish manual procedure requiring SA/ISSO acknowledgment before any XO account deletion

Account removal is a high-risk event. SA/ISSO notification allows verification that removal was authorized
and prevents unauthorized account deletion from going undetected.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account removal notifications
are handled by enterprise LDAP/AD procedures. ISSO must verify AD procedures include SA/ISSO notification on
account removal per DoD account management policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222421">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured and no account enabling events in the
systemd journal for the last 7 days.

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO/ISSM must verify:
1. Enable the XO audit plugin (xo-server-audit) to capture account enable/unlock events
2. Confirm audit logs are forwarded to a centralized SIEM
3. Test by unlocking/re-enabling an account and verifying the event is logged

When an account is re-enabled in XO (e.g., after lockout), the event should be captured by the audit plugin
and logged with the account name, timestamp, and the admin who performed the action.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account enabling events are
managed by enterprise LDAP/AD. Account unlock events in AD appear as Event ID 4767 (user account unlocked).

ISSO must verify AD audit policy covers account management and logs are retained per DoD policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found account enabling events in the systemd journal. XO is logging account
enabling activity as required. ISSO should verify audit log retention and centralized forwarding.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222422">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no auth-ldap plugin configured. XO does not natively notify SA/ISSO
when accounts are enabled/unlocked.

ACTION REQUIRED - Implement a compensating control for account enabling notifications:
Option 1: Configure SIEM to alert SA/ISSO when XO audit log records an account enable/unlock event
Option 2: Require account enable requests through ITSM with automatic SA/ISSO notification
Option 3: Establish manual procedure requiring SA/ISSO acknowledgment for any account re-enablement

Account re-enablement after lockout should be tracked to detect potential brute-force unlock attempts.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan detected the auth-ldap plugin is configured. Account enabling notifications
are handled by enterprise LDAP/AD procedures. ISSO must verify AD procedures include SA/ISSO notification on
account enabling actions per DoD account management policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222423">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan identified the following data elements managed by Xen Orchestra that require
data protection classification and documentation:

- User credentials (bcrypt-hashed passwords stored in LevelDB at /var/lib/xo-server)
- Authentication tokens (stored in memory/Redis, scoped to session)
- VM configuration data (stored in LevelDB, includes network configs, storage paths)
- XCP-ng host connection credentials (stored in LevelDB, may include passwords)
- SSL/TLS private keys (stored at /etc/ssl or /opt/xo)
- Audit log records (stored via xo-server-audit plugin)

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO must produce documentation that:
1. Identifies each data element and its sensitivity/classification level
2. Documents the protection requirements for each element (encryption, access control, retention)
3. Describes implemented protections (TLS in transit, file permissions, key management)
4. Is reviewed annually and updated when the application changes

This documentation is required by APSC-DV-000440 and must be available for auditor review.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222424">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated scan found no explicit data mining detection controls configured in Xen Orchestra.

ACTION REQUIRED - ISSO must provide one of the following:
Option A (Not Applicable determination): If the organization has determined that data mining protections are not
required for the XO management plane (e.g., because it only stores hypervisor management metadata, not sensitive
user data), document this determination with ISSO/ISSM signature and reference in the System Security Plan.

Option B (Detection controls): If data mining protections are required, implement:
1. Rate limiting: Configure XO API rate limits to detect/prevent bulk data extraction
2. SIEM monitoring: Alert on unusually high API call volumes from a single user/IP
3. Session monitoring: Track and alert on bulk VM/storage enumeration operations
4. Access logging: Ensure all API access is logged with user identity for forensic analysis

XO REST API calls are logged when the audit plugin is enabled, providing a baseline for anomaly detection.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222425">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222426">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra implements Role-Based Access Control (RBAC) with Admin, Operator, Viewer,
and No Access roles per resource pool. It does not implement Discretionary Access Control (DAC),
which requires subjects (users) to set permissions on objects they own (e.g., Unix file ACLs,
Windows DACLs). In XO, all access control is centrally administered by administrators, not by
object owners. The STIG check states: "If the application does not implement DAC, this requirement
is N/A." This requirement is Not Applicable to Xen Orchestra.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222427">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra is a virtualization management platform and does not implement information
flow control policies within the system. It does not enforce data classification labels, security
levels (e.g., Unclassified/Secret/Top Secret), or mandatory access control (MAC/MLS) for data
flowing between application components. XO's API enforces RBAC for access control but does not
enforce information flow based on sensitivity labels. The STIG check states: "If the application
does not provide data flow control capabilities, this requirement is N/A." This requirement is
Not Applicable to Xen Orchestra.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222428">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra communicates with XCP-ng hosts via XAPI (XML-RPC over TLS) but does not
implement information flow control policies between interconnected systems. It does not enforce
data classification-based flow control, cross-domain transfer guards, or security label
enforcement on data crossing system boundaries. XO enforces TLS encryption and RBAC for
inter-system API calls but not classification-based flow control. The STIG check states: "If the
application does not provide data flow control capabilities, this requirement is N/A." This
requirement is Not Applicable to Xen Orchestra.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222429">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The xo-server process runs as a dedicated non-root service account (not UID 0). XO also
enforces RBAC at the application layer: non-privileged users (Operator, Viewer roles) cannot
disable security safeguards, modify system configuration, manage encryption keys, or perform
administrative functions. The application-level privilege separation is enforced by the XO API
regardless of the OS user account used to start the service. Automated check confirmed process
owner is non-root with no membership in privileged OS groups (sudo/wheel/adm).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The xo-server process is running as root (UID 0) or a privileged OS account. This means
all XO users inherit elevated OS privileges, violating the principle of least privilege.

Remediation steps:
1. Create a dedicated service account: useradd -r -s /bin/false xo-server
2. Set ownership: chown -R xo-server:xo-server /opt/xo /var/lib/xo-server
3. Update systemd unit file to run as the service account:
   [Service]
   User=xo-server
   Group=xo-server
4. Reload and restart: systemctl daemon-reload &amp;&amp; systemctl restart xo-server
5. Verify process owner: ps -eo user,comm | grep node

Note: XO application-level RBAC (Admin/Operator/Viewer roles) is independent of the OS
process user and should remain functional after this change.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222430">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222431">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The XO audit plugin is installed and loaded. Privileged function executions are recorded
in audit logs including: user account creation/modification/deletion, ACL assignments, server
additions/removals, plugin configuration changes, and user sign-in/sign-out events. Each audit
record includes the action type, timestamp, and the user who performed it. Audit records are
accessible via the REST API at /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records and are also written to the
systemd journal under the xo-server unit.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The XO audit plugin was not detected as loaded, or audit records of privileged function
executions could not be confirmed. Privileged function executions (user management, config changes,
key management) must be recorded with the action, date, and time.

Remediation steps:
1. Install the XO audit plugin if not present:
   cd /opt/xo &amp;&amp; yarn add @xen-orchestra/audit-core
2. Enable the audit plugin in XO web UI: Settings &gt; Plugins &gt; audit &gt; Enable
3. Configure audit log retention in the plugin settings
4. Verify by performing a privileged action (e.g., create a test user) and checking:
   GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records?limit=10
5. Confirm the action, date/time, and user are recorded in the response

Note: If LDAP/AD authentication is used, ensure authentication events are also captured
in the centralized audit server per V-222422 requirements.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222432">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222433">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Account unlock process requires ISSO/ISSM interview verification. The process cannot be
fully automated. The approved account unlock procedure must meet all of the following criteria:

Required procedure elements (STIG requirement):
1. Written procedure document with ISSO and ISSM approval signatures
2. Identity verification step — administrator must confirm user identity before unlocking
3. Ticket/request workflow creating an auditable trail for each unlock event
4. Documentation of the business justification for the unlock

XO Account Unlock Methods available to the administrator:
- Web UI: Admin &gt; Users &gt; select user &gt; toggle "Enabled" state
- CLI: xo-cli user.set id=&lt;user-uuid&gt; enabled=true
- API: PATCH /rest/v0/users/&lt;uuid&gt; {"enabled": true}

To satisfy this requirement:
1. Create a Standard Operating Procedure (SOP) document for account unlocks
2. Obtain ISSO and ISSM approval and signatures on the SOP
3. Implement a ticketing workflow (e.g., ServiceNow, JIRA) for unlock requests
4. Train administrators on the identity verification step
5. Retain records of all unlock events for audit purposes</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222434">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The Standard Mandatory DoD Notice and Consent Banner is displayed on the XO login page
before granting access. Automated check confirmed banner keywords are present in the login page
HTML. The approved DoD banner text includes the required elements: notification of monitoring,
prohibition of unauthorized use, and user consent to monitoring conditions.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The DoD Notice and Consent Banner was not detected on the XO login page. XO Community
Edition does not include a built-in banner feature. The banner must be implemented via one of
the following methods:

Option 1 — Nginx reverse proxy pre-authentication page (recommended):
1. Install nginx: apt-get install -y nginx
2. Create a consent page that displays the DoD banner with an Accept button
3. Configure nginx to require banner acknowledgment before proxying to XO:
   - Serve consent.html at /
   - Redirect to /xo/ after acceptance (using a session cookie)
4. Configure XO to listen only on localhost (127.0.0.1)
5. Test: browse to XO URL and verify banner appears before login page

Option 2 — Network-level pre-authentication page:
Configure a captive portal or network access control system to present the banner
before granting network access to the XO server.

Required DoD banner text (abbreviated — use full approved text):
"You are accessing a U.S. Government (USG) Information System (IS) that is provided for
USG-authorized use only. By using this IS, you consent to monitoring of your use..."

Reference: DoD CIO memorandum on Standard Mandatory DoD Notice and Consent Banner.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222435">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The DoD Notice and Consent Banner is retained on screen until the user explicitly
acknowledges it. An acknowledgment mechanism (Accept button, checkbox, or equivalent) is present
on the banner page. Users cannot proceed to the XO login page until they take an explicit action
to accept the banner. Automated check confirmed both banner text and acknowledgment keywords are
present in the login page or pre-authentication page.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The DoD banner acknowledgment mechanism was not detected. The banner must be retained until
the user takes an explicit action to accept it — simply displaying it without requiring
acknowledgment does not satisfy this requirement.

Implementation requirements:
1. The banner page must include an explicit acceptance mechanism (one of):
   - A checkbox: "I acknowledge and accept the above terms" + Submit button
   - An "I Accept" button that the user must click to proceed
   - A typed-acknowledgment field requiring the user to type "I AGREE"
2. The banner must block access to the XO login page until accepted
3. A session cookie should be set after acknowledgment to avoid repeated banners per session

Sample nginx consent page implementation:
- Serve a consent.html with the full DoD banner text
- Include: &lt;input type="checkbox" id="accept"&gt; I acknowledge these terms
  &lt;button onclick="if(document.getElementById('accept').checked){window.location='/xo/'}"&gt;Continue&lt;/button&gt;
- Block direct access to /xo/ without the consent cookie set

Note: Both V-222434 (display banner) and V-222435 (require acknowledgment) must be satisfied
simultaneously. Implementing both with a single nginx pre-auth page is the recommended approach.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222436">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected DoD mandatory notice and consent banner content on the XO login page. The banner includes required DoD keywords. ISSO action: Verify the full banner text matches the DoD Standard Mandatory Notice and Consent Banner exactly. Document the banner source (nginx consent page, reverse proxy redirect, or application-level splash page).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No DoD mandatory notice and consent banner was detected on the XO login page. Xen Orchestra does not include a native pre-login banner mechanism. ISSO action: Implement a DoD consent banner via one of the following methods: (1) Nginx reverse proxy consent page before forwarding to XO; (2) XO customization via GUI/branding plugin; (3) Network access point banner (router/firewall warning). The banner must include: unauthorized use is prohibited, activities are monitored, evidence of unauthorized use may result in criminal prosecution. Reference VATES_COMPLIANCE_BLOCKERS.md BANNER-001 for implementation guidance.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222437">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected last successful logon display on the XO application. The application presents the time/date of the user's last successful logon after authentication. ISSO action: Verify the last logon display is visible to users immediately after login and includes at minimum the date and time of the previous successful authentication.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra does not display the time and date of the user's last successful logon. ISSO action: Implement last logon display via one of the following: (1) XO custom plugin that queries audit records for last login event; (2) Nginx/reverse proxy post-login redirect with last logon information; (3) LDAP/AD integration that surfaces last logon from directory services. Document this as an accepted risk or submit a waiver if implementation is not feasible. Reference VATES_COMPLIANCE_BLOCKERS.md BANNER-001 for related guidance.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222438">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check confirmed XO provides non-repudiation through user-attributed audit records. The XO audit plugin captures each action with userId, action type, and timestamp. ISSO action: Verify audit records cannot be modified or deleted by users whose actions are recorded. Document the audit record retention policy and integrity protection mechanisms.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Non-repudiation for XO user actions requires manual verification. XO audit plugin records user actions with userId attribution but does not cryptographically sign individual records. ISSO action: (1) Verify XO audit plugin is active and recording all user actions; (2) Verify audit records are protected from modification (immutable storage or SIEM forwarding); (3) Verify records contain sufficient attribution (userId, timestamp, action, target); (4) Consider forwarding audit records to a SIEM for integrity protection. Document the non-repudiation controls as compensating measures in the ATO package.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222439">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>System clock is synchronized via NTP/Chrony. XO audit records use the synchronized system clock for timestamping, enabling time-correlated aggregation with audit records from other systems. ISSO action: Verify NTP is synchronized to an authoritative government time source. Document the NTP server configuration and synchronization frequency.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>NTP time synchronization not confirmed for this system. Without synchronized clocks, audit records from multiple systems cannot be reliably correlated. ISSO action: (1) Configure chronyd or systemd-timesyncd to use DoD-approved NTP servers; (2) Verify synchronization: timedatectl show | grep NTPSynchronized; (3) Set polling interval appropriate for the organization tolerance level; (4) Document the authoritative time source in the system security plan.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222441">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records when session IDs are created (user login). The XO audit plugin records authentication events including user login, which creates a new session. Journal logs confirm session creation events are captured with user identity and timestamp. ISSO action: Verify audit records for session creation include: user ID, source IP, timestamp, and outcome.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Session ID creation audit record generation requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Verify XO audit plugin is installed and active; (2) Perform a test login and verify an audit record was created; (3) Confirm the audit record includes: userId, action=session.signIn, timestamp, IP address; (4) Verify audit records are retained per the organization retention policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222442">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records when session IDs are destroyed (user logout). The XO audit plugin records logout events (session.signOut) with user identity and timestamp. Session destruction events are captured when users explicitly log out or tokens expire. ISSO action: Verify audit records for session destruction include: user ID, timestamp, and session identifier.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Session ID destruction audit record generation requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Verify XO audit plugin is installed and active; (2) Perform a test logout and verify an audit record was created; (3) Confirm the audit record includes: userId, action=session.signOut, timestamp; (4) Verify session expiration (timeout) also generates an audit record.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222443">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records when session IDs are renewed. Session renewal or token refresh events are captured in the audit trail. ISSO action: Verify the audit plugin captures token renewal events and confirm the records include userId, session identifier, and timestamp.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Session ID renewal audit record generation requires manual verification. XO may use rolling session tokens without explicit renewal audit records. ISSO action: (1) Review XO session management configuration (config.toml session settings); (2) Verify whether token renewal generates an audit event; (3) If no renewal audit exists, document as accepted risk or implement via custom logging middleware; (4) Consider enabling rolling session logging in the XO configuration.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222444">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No sensitive data (passwords, credentials, tokens) detected in XO application logs. XO Winston logger does not record authentication credentials or session tokens in log output. ISSO action: Periodically review logs to confirm no sensitive data is written. Verify the Winston log level is set to exclude debug-level password data in production.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Possible sensitive data detected in XO application logs. ISSO action: (1) Review the flagged log files for actual sensitive data exposure; (2) Verify NODE_ENV=production is set (suppresses verbose debug logging); (3) Review Winston logger configuration for log level and format settings; (4) Ensure authentication middleware does not log passwords or tokens; (5) Implement log scrubbing if sensitive data is confirmed in logs.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222445">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records when sessions time out. Session timeout events are captured in the audit trail with user identity and timestamp. ISSO action: Verify audit records for session timeouts include: userId, session identifier, and the reason for termination (timeout vs explicit logout).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Session timeout audit record generation requires manual verification. Session timeout events may not generate distinct audit records in XO. ISSO action: (1) Configure session timeout in XO (config.toml or environment variables); (2) Test session timeout and verify an audit/log event is generated; (3) If no timeout audit exists, implement via session expiration middleware; (4) Document as compensating control if session timeout logging is not natively supported.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222446">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records include timestamps for all events. systemd journal entries have system timestamps; XO audit plugin uses Unix millisecond timestamps. Winston logger produces ISO 8601 formatted timestamps. ISSO action: Verify all audit record sources (journal, XO audit, nginx access log) include timestamps with sufficient granularity (seconds or better).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Timestamp recording in XO audit records requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Retrieve a sample audit record: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records?limit=5; (2) Verify each record has a time field in Unix milliseconds; (3) Verify systemd journal entries include system timestamps; (4) Verify Winston log format includes timestamp configuration.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222447">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records that include HTTP headers (User-Agent, method, path). Nginx access logs are configured to capture User-Agent, Referer, and HTTP method. ISSO action: Verify the nginx combined log format is active and access logs are retained per the organization audit log retention policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>HTTP header audit record generation requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Verify nginx access_log is enabled with combined format (includes User-Agent, Referer); (2) Verify the log_format includes: $remote_addr, $request, $status, $http_user_agent, $http_referer; (3) If XO is accessed directly (no nginx), verify XO/Express.js logs HTTP headers via morgan middleware; (4) Retain nginx access logs per organizational policy (minimum 1 year for DoD systems).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222448">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records that include connecting system IP addresses. Nginx access logs capture client IP ($remote_addr) and X-Forwarded-For headers. ISSO action: Verify client IP addresses are accurately recorded even when behind a load balancer or reverse proxy (trust proxy setting may be required in Express.js).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Connecting system IP address audit record generation requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Verify nginx access_log captures $remote_addr for each request; (2) If behind a load balancer, configure nginx real_ip_header to capture original client IP; (3) Verify XO audit plugin records the requesting IP address in each audit record; (4) Test with a known client IP and confirm it appears in access logs.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222449">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records include the username/user ID for each event. The XO audit plugin records the userId for every action in the audit trail. ISSO action: Verify each audit record includes a non-null userId field. Confirm that unauthenticated actions (failed logins) record the attempted username.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Username/user ID in audit records requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Retrieve a sample audit record: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records?limit=5; (2) Verify each record has a userId or subject field identifying the user; (3) Perform a test action and verify the audit record contains your user ID; (4) Verify failed authentication attempts also record the attempted username.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222450">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records for privilege grant attempts. The XO audit plugin logs ACL changes, role assignments, and permission modifications. Both successful and unsuccessful privilege grant attempts are captured with userId and timestamp. ISSO action: Verify audit records for privilege changes include: granting user ID, target user ID, privilege granted, and outcome.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Privilege grant attempt audit record generation requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Verify XO audit plugin is active and logging ACL/permission changes; (2) Test: assign a role to a user and verify an audit record is created; (3) Confirm the audit record includes: userId (granter), targetUserId, action, privilege level; (4) Verify failed privilege escalation attempts also generate audit records.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222451">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records for security object access attempts. The XO audit plugin logs all user interactions with security objects (VMs, hosts, storage, networks). Both successful and unsuccessful access attempts are recorded with userId and timestamp. ISSO action: Verify audit records for security object access include: userId, object type/ID, action performed, and outcome (success/failure).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Security object access audit record generation requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Verify XO audit plugin is active and logging resource access events; (2) Test: access a VM and verify an audit record is created; (3) Test: attempt access to a resource without permission and verify audit record is created; (4) Confirm audit records include: userId, objectType, objectId, action, outcome.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222452">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO generates audit records for security level access attempts. XO uses RBAC (Admin, Operator, Viewer roles) rather than MAC security levels. The XO audit plugin logs all actions with role context, capturing access attempts at different privilege levels. ISSO action: Verify audit records reflect the user role level and capture both authorized and unauthorized access attempts across privilege boundaries.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Security level access audit record generation requires manual verification. ISSO action: (1) Verify XO audit plugin is active and logging RBAC role-based access events; (2) Test: attempt an admin-only action with a viewer account and verify audit record is created; (3) Confirm audit records capture cross-role access attempts; (4) Document XO RBAC model as the mechanism satisfying security level access control audit requirement.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222453">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra does not implement data classification categories, MAC security labels, or compartmentalized data protection. XO is a virtualization management platform that uses RBAC (Admin/Operator/Viewer roles) — not data classification levels. The STIG check explicitly states this requirement is not applicable when the application does not require compartmentalized data and data protection. This condition applies to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222454">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active. The XO audit plugin records all ACL and role modification events (addAcl, removeAcl, setAcl) which constitute privilege modification attempts in XO's RBAC model. Both successful and unsuccessful privilege modification attempts are captured with userId, action type, timestamp, and target object.
ISSO action: Verify audit records include the granting user ID, target user/object, privilege modified, and outcome. Confirm audit records are retained per the organization retention policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active. Privilege modification audit records may not be generated.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Test: assign and revoke a role for a test user; (3) Verify audit records capture: userId (admin performing change), targetUserId, action (addAcl/removeAcl), privilege level, and outcome; (4) Verify failed privilege modification attempts also generate audit records.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222455">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra does not implement classified security objects or data elements with privilege/classification designations. XO manages virtual infrastructure resources (VMs, hosts, storage, networks) using RBAC access controls, not object-level security classification labels. This requirement for security object modification auditing does not apply to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222456">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra uses RBAC (Admin/Operator/Viewer) and does not implement MAC security levels, security domains, or multilevel security (MLS) classifications. RBAC role changes (privilege modifications) are audited under V-222454. This MAC-specific security level modification requirement does not apply to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222457">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra does not store or process classified information and does not implement data classification categories or compartmentalized data protection. The STIG check explicitly states this requirement is not applicable when the application does not require compartmentalized data protection. This condition applies to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222458">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active. The XO audit plugin records all ACL and role deletion events (removeAcl, deleteAcl operations) which constitute privilege deletion attempts in XO's RBAC model. Both successful and unsuccessful privilege deletion attempts are captured with userId, action type, timestamp, and target.
ISSO action: Verify audit records include the user performing the deletion, the target user/object, the privilege deleted, and the outcome. Confirm audit records are retained per the organization retention policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active. Privilege deletion audit records may not be generated.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Test: remove a role from a test user; (3) Verify audit records capture: userId (admin), targetUserId, action (removeAcl), privilege level, and outcome; (4) Verify failed deletion attempts also generate audit records.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222459">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra uses RBAC (Admin/Operator/Viewer) and does not implement MAC security levels or multilevel security domains. The deletion of security level permissions is not a supported operation in XO. RBAC role removals (privilege deletions) are audited under V-222458. This MAC-specific requirement does not apply to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222460">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra stores its state in LevelDB (a key-value store) and does not implement a relational database with security-labeled objects or data elements. XO does not support compartmentalized data classification for database records. This database security object deletion requirement does not apply to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222461">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra does not store classified or categorized information and does not implement data classification categories. The STIG check explicitly states this requirement is not applicable when the application does not require compartmentalized data and data protection. This condition applies to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222462">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active. XO records session.signIn events for all authentication attempts. The audit plugin captures: userId, action (session.signIn), timestamp, source IP address, and outcome. Failed authentication attempts are also recorded. systemd journal provides additional authentication event logging.
ISSO action: Verify audit records include successful logins (userId + timestamp) and failed login attempts (attempted username + reason). Confirm records are retained per the organization retention policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active. Logon attempt audit records may not be generated.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Perform a successful login and verify session.signIn audit record was created; (3) Perform a failed login and verify it is recorded; (4) Confirm records include: userId, action=session.signIn, timestamp, source IP, outcome.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222463">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active. XO audit plugin captures all privileged activities including: VM lifecycle operations (start/stop/snapshot/migrate), host management (patch/reboot/maintenance), user management, ACL changes, server configuration, and pool operations. All records include userId, action, target object ID, and timestamp.
ISSO action: Verify audit records capture the full range of admin operations. Test by performing a VM snapshot as admin and confirm the audit record shows your userId, the action, and the VM ID.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active. Privileged activity audit records may not be generated.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Perform a privileged action (start a VM, add a user, change an ACL); (3) Verify audit record includes: userId, action type, target object, timestamp; (4) Verify system-level access events (host management, pool operations) are captured.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222464">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active. XO records session.signIn (session start) and session.signOut (session end) events with Unix millisecond timestamps for each user session. Session start and end times are available in the XO audit trail via the REST API.
ISSO action: Query the audit API: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records?limit=10 and verify records include 'time' field in Unix milliseconds. Confirm session.signIn and session.signOut pairs are present for the same userId.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active. Session start/end time audit records may not be generated.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Perform a login and logout; (3) Verify audit records for session.signIn and session.signOut exist with timestamps; (4) Confirm timestamps have millisecond granularity and are in UTC.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222465">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active. XO audit plugin records all object access events including VM operations (start/stop/snapshot/migrate/console), host management, storage repository access, network configuration, and pool membership changes. Both successful and authorized operations are recorded. Unauthorized access attempts return errors which are logged by the application.
ISSO action: Test object access logging by accessing a VM and verifying the audit record includes: userId, action, objectType (vm/host/sr/network), objectId, and timestamp.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active. Object access audit records may not be generated.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Access a VM (start or view console); (3) Verify audit record includes: userId, action, object type, object ID, timestamp; (4) Test unauthorized access (attempt restricted action) and verify the failed attempt is also recorded.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222466">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra is a web-based virtualization management application. Users interact with XO exclusively via HTTPS web UI and REST API. XO does not expose terminal emulators, command shells, file system browsers, or direct OS command execution interfaces to authenticated users. The STIG check explicitly states this requirement is not applicable when the application does not provide direct access to the system. This condition applies to XO deployments.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222467">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active and XO is not configured with LDAP enterprise authentication. XO audit plugin records user account lifecycle events: user.create, user.set (modify), and user.delete operations are captured with userId (admin performing action), target userId, action type, and timestamp.
ISSO action: Test account lifecycle logging: (1) Create a test user and verify audit record; (2) Modify the user and verify; (3) Delete the user and verify. Confirm each event includes: adminUserId, targetUserId, action, and timestamp.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active or account lifecycle events are logged. Account lifecycle audit records may not be generated.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Create, modify, and delete a test user account; (3) Verify audit records for each lifecycle event are created; (4) Confirm records include: performing user ID, target user ID, action, and timestamp.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO is configured to use LDAP/AD enterprise authentication. The STIG states this requirement is not applicable when the application uses a STIG-compliant enterprise user management capability. Account lifecycle events (create/modify/disable/terminate) are managed and audited by the enterprise directory (AD/LDAP) system. Verify the enterprise directory STIG compliance and confirm account lifecycle audit records exist in the directory audit logs.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222468">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check confirmed the XO audit plugin is present and the XO service is active under systemd. The audit plugin is loaded with the XO application on startup. Winston logger initializes with the application and begins logging from the first event. systemd journals service start events capturing the startup sequence.
ISSO action: Verify session auditing begins on startup by reviewing systemd journal entries: journalctl -u xo-server --since 'last reboot' | head -20. Confirm log entries begin immediately upon service start.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active or that session auditing begins on startup.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Restart the xo-server service: systemctl restart xo-server; (3) Review logs immediately after restart: journalctl -u xo-server -f; (4) Verify the first log entries appear immediately upon service start; (5) Confirm the audit plugin logs a startup event.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222469">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check confirmed the XO service runs under systemd which records all service stop/shutdown events in the system journal. systemd logs both graceful shutdown (systemctl stop xo-server) and unexpected termination events with timestamps. This provides comprehensive shutdown event logging.
ISSO action: Review recent shutdown events: journalctl -u xo-server | grep -i 'stop\|shut\|deactiv' | tail -10. Verify shutdown events are captured with timestamp and reason.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm systemd manages the XO service or that shutdown events are logged.
ISSO action: (1) Verify xo-server runs as a systemd service: systemctl status xo-server; (2) Stop and start the service to generate shutdown events; (3) Verify: journalctl -u xo-server | grep -i stopped; (4) Confirm shutdown events include: timestamp, service name, and exit status; (5) If not systemd-managed, configure XO to log shutdown events via Winston.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
    <Vuln ID="V-222470">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check detected the XO audit plugin is active and XO configuration references outbound connections to XCP-ng hosts. XO audit records include source IP (connecting client) and target object references (host IDs which map to destination IPs). Outbound connections to XCP-ng hosts via XAPI are logged per-operation in XO audit records.
ISSO action: Verify destination IP logging by checking audit records for host operations: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records?limit=20. Confirm records reference the destination XCP-ng host by ID (which can be resolved to IP via server list).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Automated check could not confirm the XO audit plugin is active or that destination IP addresses are logged for outbound connections.
ISSO action: (1) Install and activate the @xen-orchestra/audit plugin; (2) Perform an operation on a VM hosted on a specific XCP-ng host; (3) Verify the audit record references the target host (which maps to the destination IP); (4) Check nginx access logs for upstream proxy destination logging; (5) Review syslog for outbound connection destination IPs to DNS, LDAP, and XCP-ng hosts.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222471">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO provides audit logging of user data access operations. The XO audit plugin (@xen-orchestra/audit) is installed and records all user API operations, including read/list/get actions that constitute data access. Each audit record includes the action name (API method), userId of the authenticated user, and timestamp. All data access is performed via the XO JSON-RPC API, and the audit plugin intercepts all API calls at the middleware layer.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm XO audit plugin is enabled in XO web UI (Settings &gt; Plugins &gt; Audit)
2. Review audit records via API: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records
3. Verify read-type actions (vm.list, host.get, etc.) are present in audit records
4. Confirm audit records are retained per organizational policy (minimum 1 year for DoD)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit logging of user data access operations was not confirmed. The XO audit plugin may not be installed or enabled.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Install XO audit plugin: In XO web UI, go to Settings &gt; Plugins
2. Find '@xen-orchestra/audit' or 'audit' plugin and enable it
3. For XOCE: npm install @xen-orchestra/audit in the XO packages directory
4. Verify the plugin logs user data access events after enabling
5. Test by performing a data access operation and reviewing audit records

ALTERNATIVE: If using a SIEM or external logging solution that captures all XO API calls, provide documentation showing data access events are captured and attributed to users.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222472">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO provides audit logging of user data change operations. The XO audit plugin (@xen-orchestra/audit) records all create, update, and delete API operations. Each modification action (vm.create, vm.set, vm.delete, acl.add, acl.remove, etc.) is logged with the full action name, authenticated userId, and timestamp.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm XO audit plugin is enabled in XO web UI (Settings &gt; Plugins &gt; Audit)
2. Perform a change operation (e.g., start a VM, modify a setting)
3. Verify the change appears in audit records: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records
4. Confirm the record includes: action name, userId, and timestamp
5. Retain audit records per organizational policy (minimum 1 year for DoD)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit logging of user data change operations was not confirmed. The XO audit plugin may not be installed or enabled.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Install and enable XO audit plugin via XO web UI (Settings &gt; Plugins)
2. For XOCE deployments: install @xen-orchestra/audit package
3. Verify change operations (create/update/delete) are captured in audit records
4. Test by creating or modifying a resource and checking audit log

If application design documents specify protected data elements, verify those specific elements' changes are also captured. Consult XO documentation for audit plugin configuration.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222473">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records include date and time stamps on all log entries. systemd journal provides precise ISO 8601 timestamps (YYYY-MM-DDTHH:MM:SS+TZ) for all xo-server events as a function of the journald service. Timestamps are added at the kernel level and cannot be disabled without disabling journald.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Run: journalctl -u xo-server --no-pager -n 10 --output=short-iso
2. Confirm each line has an ISO 8601 timestamp prefix
3. If using file-based logging: tail -5 /var/log/xo-server.log
4. Note: Per V-222425, timestamps should use UTC/GMT for DoD compliance
   (local timezone detected as non-UTC - separate finding)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Date/time stamps in XO audit records could not be confirmed by automated check. Manual verification is required.

VERIFICATION STEPS:
1. Access the system: ssh root@xo1
2. Review journal: journalctl -u xo-server --no-pager -n 20 --output=short-iso
3. Verify each audit entry has a date/time stamp
4. Review log files if file-based logging is configured

If timestamps are absent, configure application or application server to include date and time in all audit log entries.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222474">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records identify which component, feature, or function triggered each audit event. The XO audit plugin records the API action name (e.g., 'vm.create', 'acl.add', 'user.set') for each logged event. This action name identifies the specific XO component and operation that triggered the audit record. The systemd journal additionally tags all entries with _SYSTEMD_UNIT=xo-server.service as the source component.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Review audit records: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records?limit=10
2. Verify each record includes an 'action' field (e.g., 'vm.start', 'host.get')
3. Confirm the action name identifies the XO feature/function that triggered the event
4. Document key XO components: web server (express), API server (xo-server),    database (LevelDB), session store (Redis)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records identifying the triggering component/function were not confirmed. Manual review of application documentation and logs is required.

VERIFICATION STEPS:
1. Obtain architecture documentation identifying XO components:
   - Web/API server: xo-server (Node.js/Express)
   - Data store: LevelDB at /var/lib/xo-server
   - Session store: Redis
   - Authentication: local + optional LDAP/SAML plugins
2. Access audit logs and verify component identification in entries
3. If XO audit plugin is not installed, install it to enable structured audit records
   with action names identifying the triggering component/function</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222475">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO is configured with centralized logging AND includes a unique application identifier in forwarded log entries. The hostname and application name (xo-server) are included in all log entries forwarded to the centralized logging solution.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify centralized logging configuration: grep -rE '@@?' /etc/rsyslog.conf /etc/rsyslog.d/
2. Confirm forwarded entries include hostname: check rsyslog template or default format
3. Verify application name (xo-server) is identifiable in centralized log entries
4. Test by reviewing a sample of centralized log entries for XO source identification</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO is configured with centralized logging but a unique application identifier was not confirmed in the forwarded log entries.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Configure rsyslog/syslog-ng to include hostname and program name in all log entries
2. Example rsyslog template: $template CustomFormat,"%HOSTNAME% %programname% %msg%
"
3. Verify xo-server is identifiable as the application in centralized log storage
4. Coordinate with SIEM team to confirm XO logs are distinguishable from other sources</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. XO is not configured to use a centralized logging solution. Per STIG check content: if the application logs locally and does not utilize a centralized logging solution, this requirement is Not Applicable.

XO currently logs to the local systemd journal and/or local log files only. No remote syslog, syslog-ng, or systemd-journal-upload destinations are configured.

NOTE: For DoD environments, configuring centralized audit log forwarding is strongly recommended to satisfy V-222481 (off-load audit records) and support SIEM integration. See VATES_COMPLIANCE_BLOCKERS.md for implementation guidance.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222476">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records include event outcome information. The XO audit plugin records action results, including error conditions. The systemd journal captures success/error states for xo-server operations. Successful API calls are logged by the audit plugin; errors are logged by both the audit plugin and the application-level error handlers.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Review audit records for outcome fields: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records
2. Check for error records: journalctl -u xo-server -n 50 | grep -i 'error\|fail'
3. Verify successful operations are also captured (implied by default per STIG)
4. Document that success events may be implied if documented as organizational baseline</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Event outcome information in XO audit records was not confirmed. Manual verification of audit log format is required.

VERIFICATION STEPS:
1. Perform both a successful and a failed operation in XO
2. Review audit records and confirm both outcomes are captured
3. Verify the audit plugin records error conditions and success states

REMEDIATION: Install/enable XO audit plugin to capture structured audit records that include event outcomes. Configure application error handlers to log failure details.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222477">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records include user identity information for all events. The XO audit plugin records the authenticated userId (XO user account ID) for every API action. This userId is the primary identity associated with each audit event, establishing accountability for all privileged and non-privileged operations.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Review audit records: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records?limit=10
2. Verify each record includes a 'userId' field with the authenticated user's ID
3. Cross-reference userId with XO user accounts: GET /rest/v0/users
4. For LDAP/AD users, verify userId maps to the AD account identity
5. Confirm system-level processes are identified differently from user actions</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>User identity in XO audit records was not confirmed by automated check. Manual review is required.

VERIFICATION STEPS:
1. Log into XO as a test user and perform an action
2. Review audit records: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records
3. Verify the action record includes the userId of the test account

REMEDIATION: Install/enable XO audit plugin. Without the audit plugin, XO does not produce structured per-user audit records. The audit plugin is required for DoD compliance.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222478">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO audit records capture the full API action details for all privileged commands. XO uses a JSON-RPC API architecture where all privileged commands are API method calls (e.g., 'vm.create', 'vm.delete', 'acl.add', 'host.set'). The XO audit plugin records the complete method name (action) along with the authenticated userId for every privileged operation, fulfilling the full-text recording requirement.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Perform a privileged operation (create VM, modify ACL, add user)
2. Review audit records: GET /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records
3. Verify the record includes the full action name and userId
4. Confirm privileged commands (admin operations) are distinguishable from user actions
5. For group account scenarios: verify individual userId is always recorded (no shared accounts)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Full-text recording of privileged commands in XO audit records was not confirmed. Manual verification is required.

VERIFICATION STEPS:
1. Perform privileged operations as an admin user
2. Review audit records and verify full action details are captured
3. Confirm each record includes: action name, userId, timestamp, and relevant parameters

REMEDIATION: Install/enable XO audit plugin. This is the only mechanism in XO that provides structured full-text recording of privileged API commands with user attribution.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222479">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>A relational database was detected but transaction recovery logging configuration was not confirmed. Manual review of database transaction logging settings is required.

VERIFICATION STEPS:
1. Identify the database being used by XO
2. For PostgreSQL: verify WAL (Write-Ahead Logging) is enabled
   SELECT name, setting FROM pg_settings WHERE name LIKE 'wal%';
3. For MySQL/MariaDB: verify binary logging is enabled
   SHOW VARIABLES LIKE 'log_bin';
4. Document transaction log retention settings

REMEDIATION: Configure database transaction logging appropriate for the RDBMS in use. Ensure transaction logs are retained per organizational data retention policy.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. XO does not use a transaction-based relational database management system.

XO's primary data store is LevelDB (a key-value store), not an RDBMS. LevelDB provides atomic batch writes (all-or-nothing operations) but does not produce SQL transaction logs or support BEGIN/COMMIT/ROLLBACK transactions.

DATA STORE SUMMARY:
- Primary: LevelDB at /var/lib/xo-server (key-value, no transaction logs)
- Sessions: Redis (ephemeral session data, in-memory)
- No PostgreSQL, MySQL, MariaDB, or SQLite detected

This check applies to transaction-based applications using RDBMS backends with SQL transaction logging requirements. XO's LevelDB architecture is not in scope.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222480">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No enterprise centralized logging solution was detected. Manual review of XO audit configuration management capability is required.

VERIFICATION STEPS:
1. Review XO audit plugin configuration in XO web UI (Settings &gt; Plugins &gt; Audit)
2. Verify the audit plugin provides centralized configuration of audit record content
3. Document what audit events are captured and how content is managed
4. If a SIEM or centralized log management system is used (even if not detected by    automated check), provide documentation to satisfy this requirement

REMEDIATION: Configure rsyslog or syslog-ng to forward XO logs to an enterprise centralized logging solution. Enterprise SIEM tools (Splunk, ELK, QRadar) provide centralized management of audit record content collection and configuration.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. XO is configured to log to an enterprise centralized logging solution that meets this requirement.

Per STIG check content: if the application is configured to log application event entries to a centralized, enterprise-based logging solution, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized logging destination is an approved enterprise solution
2. Verify XO audit records are being forwarded to the centralized system
3. Document the centralized logging architecture (rsyslog/syslog-ng target server)
4. Confirm the centralized solution provides configuration management of audit content</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222481">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No audit log off-loading to a different system was detected. XO audit records are currently stored only on the local system.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Configure rsyslog to forward XO logs to a centralized audit server:
   echo '*.* @@audit-server.example.com:514' &gt;&gt; /etc/rsyslog.d/90-xo-remote.conf
   systemctl restart rsyslog
2. For journal-based forwarding: configure systemd-journal-upload to forward to
   a systemd-journal-remote server
3. Alternatively, configure logrotate postrotate scripts to rsync/scp logs to
   a designated log archive server
4. Verify automated tasks run per approved schedule to transfer audit records

Obtain risk acceptance documentation if off-loading cannot be implemented immediately. Document compensating controls (e.g., daily backup to separate media).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. XO is configured to utilize a centralized logging solution that off-loads audit records to a different system.

Per STIG check content: if the application is configured to utilize a centralized logging solution, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm audit records are being forwarded to a separate centralized log server
2. Verify the receiving system is different from the XO host being audited
3. Review log forwarding configuration: /etc/rsyslog.d/ or syslog-ng destinations
4. Confirm forwarding occurs per the approved schedule or in real-time
5. Verify receiving system has adequate capacity for log retention (DoD: 1+ year)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222482">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO application logs are being forwarded to a centralized log repository. Rsyslog remote target(s), systemd-journal-remote, or syslog-ng remote destination(s) were detected, indicating that audit records are being transmitted to a centralized log management system.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized destination is an approved enterprise logging solution
2. Verify XO audit plugin records (via /rest/v0/plugins/audit/records) are included in forwarded logs
3. Confirm log forwarding is encrypted (@@hostname = TLS-wrapped rsyslog, or equivalent)
4. Document the centralized logging architecture in the SSP
5. Retain audit records per organizational policy (minimum 1 year for DoD)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No centralized log repository configuration was detected. XO audit records are currently stored only on the local system and are not being forwarded to an enterprise centralized logging solution.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Configure rsyslog to forward logs to a centralized syslog server:
   Add to /etc/rsyslog.conf: *.* @@siem-server.domain:514
   For TLS: *.* @@(o)siem-server.domain:6514
2. Alternatively, configure systemd-journal-remote to forward journal entries
3. Enterprise SIEM options: Splunk, ELK/Elasticsearch, IBM QRadar, Graylog
4. Restart rsyslog after configuration: systemctl restart rsyslog
5. Verify forwarding: tail -f /var/log/syslog and confirm SIEM receives entries

NOTE: The XO audit plugin writes to /var/log/xo-server/ locally. Configure the SIEM to ingest these log files in addition to syslog forwarding.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222483">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No centralized logging solution was detected that provides audit storage capacity monitoring. XO does not natively alert on audit log storage reaching 75% capacity.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Configure disk usage monitoring on the log partition:
   - logwatch or logcheck with disk threshold alerts
   - Custom cron job: du -sh /var/log | awk '{if($1+0 &gt; threshold) send_alert}'
2. Configure systemd journal size limits in /etc/systemd/journald.conf:
   SystemMaxUse=2G (set based on available disk space)
   SystemKeepFree=500M
3. Implement enterprise monitoring: Nagios, Zabbix, Prometheus + Alertmanager
4. Configure alerting to SA and ISSO email addresses
5. Document the capacity monitoring procedure in the SSP

ALTERNATIVE: Deploy a centralized logging solution (rsyslog + SIEM) that provides storage capacity monitoring and automated alerting.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides audit record storage capacity monitoring.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized logging solution has capacity monitoring enabled
2. Verify alerts are configured for 75% threshold notifications to SA and ISSO
3. Document the centralized logging capacity monitoring configuration in the SSP
4. Test the alerting mechanism to confirm SA and ISSO receive notifications</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222484">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No centralized logging solution was detected that provides real-time audit failure alerting. XO does not natively send immediate real-time alerts for audit failure events.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Monitor XO service health for audit-related failures:
   journalctl -u xo-server -f | grep -i "audit\|error\|fail"
2. Configure systemd service failure alerting:
   Create /etc/systemd/system/xo-server.service.d/alert.conf with OnFailure= directive
3. Implement log monitoring with immediate alerting:
   - Logcheck or OSSEC for real-time log analysis and alerting
   - Configure to send immediate email/SMS to SA and ISSO on audit failures
4. Set XO_AUDIT_FAILURE alert in SIEM or monitoring platform
5. Document the audit failure alerting procedure in the SSP

NOTE: This applies to applications with moderate or high categorization. XO managing virtualized resources should be classified at minimum moderate impact.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides real-time audit failure alerting.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized logging/SIEM solution has real-time alerting configured
2. Verify audit failure events trigger immediate notifications to SA and ISSO
3. Document the audit failure alerting configuration in the SSP
4. Test the alerting by simulating an audit failure and confirming notifications</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222485">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No alerting mechanism was detected to notify ISSO and SA when audit processing fails. XO does not natively send alerts when the audit plugin or logging subsystem encounters a processing failure.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Configure systemd service monitoring for xo-server:
   Set up OnFailure= in xo-server.service to trigger notification on crash
2. Monitor audit plugin status via XO web UI (Settings &gt; Plugins &gt; Audit)
3. Implement Nagios/Zabbix/Prometheus check for XO service availability
4. Configure log monitoring to detect audit-related errors:
   grep -i "audit\|plugin.*error\|winston.*error" /var/log/xo-server/
5. Set up automated email/SMS alerting to SA and ISSO on detection
6. Document the alerting procedure in the Incident Response Plan

TESTING: Simulate audit failure by temporarily disabling audit plugin and verify SA/ISSO receive notification within acceptable timeframe.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides audit processing failure alerting to SA and ISSO.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized SIEM/logging solution monitors audit processing health
2. Verify alerts are routed to SA and ISSO when audit failures occur
3. Document the notification chain and escalation procedures in the SSP
4. Conduct periodic testing of audit failure alerting (at minimum annually)</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222486">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>XO does not natively shut down upon audit failure. XO will continue to operate even if the audit plugin is disabled or encounters errors. This behavior is by design to maintain hypervisor management availability, but requires documented compensating controls.

REMEDIATION/COMPENSATING CONTROLS:
1. Document the availability-override justification in the SSP:
   XO manages virtualized infrastructure; shutdown on audit failure could impact    all hosted VMs and services (availability overrides this requirement per STIG)
2. Implement compensating controls:
   a. Audit log monitoring with immediate alerting (see V-222485)
   b. Centralized logging to prevent single-point audit failure
   c. Redundant audit mechanisms (systemd journal + XO audit plugin)
3. Configure systemd watchdog for xo-server to restart on crashes:
   Add WatchdogSec=30 to xo-server.service
4. Document in POA&amp;M if full shutdown-on-failure cannot be implemented

NOTE: For hypervisor management applications, availability is typically an overriding concern. This finding should be documented with availability override justification in the system security plan.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured, providing an alternative audit mechanism that prevents the need for application shutdown upon local audit failure.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm centralized logging provides continuous audit capability even if local logging fails
2. Verify the centralized solution has high availability configuration
3. Document why centralized logging satisfies this requirement in the SSP
4. Confirm organizational risk acceptance for this control based on availability requirements</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222487">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No centralized logging solution was detected that enables central review and analysis of audit records from multiple XO components. XO audit records from xo-server, systemd journal, and nginx (if present) are stored separately locally.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Deploy a centralized log management solution:
   - ELK Stack (Elasticsearch, Logstash, Kibana) for search and analysis
   - Splunk Enterprise for correlation and centralized review
   - Graylog as open-source alternative
2. Configure log forwarding from all XO components:
   a. xo-server logs: /var/log/xo-server/ -&gt; SIEM
   b. systemd journal: rsyslog + systemd-journald forwarding
   c. Authentication logs: /var/log/auth.log -&gt; SIEM
3. Create dashboards for centralized audit record review
4. Document the centralized review capability in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides the capability to centrally review and analyze audit records from multiple XO components.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm all XO log sources are forwarded to the centralized solution:
   - xo-server application logs
   - systemd journal (authentication, service events)
   - Audit plugin records
2. Verify the centralized solution provides search and analysis capabilities
3. Confirm authorized personnel can access centralized audit records for review
4. Document the centralized logging architecture in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222488">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No centralized logging solution was detected that provides audit record filtering capability. XO does not natively provide audit record filtering by organization-defined criteria without a supporting SIEM or log management platform.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Deploy a log management solution that supports filtering:
   - Kibana (ELK Stack): create saved searches and filters
   - Splunk: use SPL queries for organization-defined criteria
   - Graylog: create streams and filters
2. Define organization-specific filtering criteria:
   - Authentication failures, privilege escalation attempts
   - VM creation/deletion events
   - Configuration changes
   - Failed API calls
3. Implement grep-based filtering for immediate review:
   journalctl -u xo-server | grep -E "error|fail|unauthorized"
4. Document filtering criteria in the Audit Policy</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides the capability to filter audit records based on organization-defined criteria.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized solution supports filtering by organization-defined criteria
2. Verify filter configurations are documented and cover DoD-required event types
3. Test filtering capability: confirm specific event types can be isolated on demand
4. Document approved filtering criteria in the Audit Policy and SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222489">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No audit reduction capability was detected that supports on-demand reporting. XO does not natively provide audit reduction tools without a supporting SIEM or log management platform.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Implement an audit reduction solution:
   - Splunk: saved reports and scheduled reports
   - ELK Kibana: dashboards with on-demand reporting
   - Graylog: reports and dashboards
2. Use command-line tools for on-demand reduction:
   journalctl --since "7 days ago" -u xo-server | grep -i "audit" | sort | uniq -c
3. Configure logrotate with compression for manageable report sizes
4. Create organization-defined report templates covering:
   - Authentication and authorization events
   - VM lifecycle operations
   - Administrative actions
5. Document reporting procedures in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides audit reduction capability supporting on-demand reporting.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized solution has on-demand report generation capability
2. Verify reports can be generated for any date range without modifying source records
3. Test by generating an on-demand report for a specific time period or event type
4. Document available report types and generation procedures in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222490">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No audit reduction capability was detected that supports on-demand audit review and analysis. XO does not natively provide audit reduction and analysis tools without a supporting SIEM or log management platform.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Implement an audit reduction and analysis solution:
   - Elasticsearch + Kibana for full-text search and analysis
   - Splunk for correlation and anomaly detection
   - OSSEC or Wazuh for host-based audit analysis
2. For immediate capability: use systemd journal analysis tools:
   journalctl -u xo-server --output=json | python3 -c "import json,sys; [print(json.dumps(json.loads(l))) for l in sys.stdin]"
3. Configure log parsing rules to extract structured data from XO logs
4. Define analysis use cases:
   - Failed authentication correlation
   - Privilege escalation patterns
   - Unusual VM operations
5. Document analysis procedures in the Incident Response Plan</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides audit reduction capability supporting on-demand audit review and analysis.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized solution supports on-demand audit record review
2. Verify analysis tools (search, correlation, aggregation) are available
3. Confirm authorized personnel can perform ad-hoc analysis of XO audit records
4. Document analysis procedures and available tool capabilities in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222491">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No audit reduction capability was detected that supports after-the-fact security incident investigations. XO audit records are stored locally without a dedicated investigation and forensics capability.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Implement log retention and audit reduction for forensic capability:
   - Configure log retention for minimum 1 year (DoD requirement)
   - logrotate: rotate monthly, retain=12
   - Centralized SIEM with long-term storage (cold tier for older records)
2. Establish forensic investigation procedures:
   - Preserve log integrity: use immutable storage or write-once media
   - Configure chattr +a on log directories to prevent deletion
3. Implement chain of custody procedures for audit records
4. Document the forensic investigation capability in the Incident Response Plan
5. Conduct periodic tabletop exercises to validate investigation capability

CRITICAL: After-the-fact investigation capability requires log records be preserved without modification. Configure append-only logging.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides audit reduction capability supporting after-the-fact security incident investigations.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm centralized log retention meets DoD minimum (1 year for most systems)
2. Verify audit records cannot be deleted or modified after collection
3. Confirm the investigation process is documented in the Incident Response Plan
4. Test the forensic capability by performing a mock incident investigation</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222492">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No report generation capability was detected that supports on-demand audit review and analysis. XO does not include a built-in audit report generation tool.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Implement a report generation solution:
   - Kibana (ELK): create and save audit dashboards as reports
   - Splunk: scheduled reports and dashboard exports
   - Custom scripts: parse XO logs and generate structured reports
2. Develop standard report templates for:
   - Weekly authentication summary report
   - VM lifecycle change report
   - Administrative action audit report
   - Security event summary
3. Implement report scheduling:
   - Cron-based: 0 8 * * 1 /usr/local/bin/generate_xo_audit_report.sh
4. Configure report distribution to ISSO and SA
5. Document report generation capability in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides report generation capability supporting on-demand audit review and analysis.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized solution has report generation capability
2. Verify reports can be generated on-demand without specialized access
3. Confirm report output includes all required audit record fields
4. Document available report types and access procedures in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222493">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No report generation capability was detected that supports on-demand reporting requirements. XO does not include built-in compliance or security reporting tools.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Implement report generation capability:
   - Deploy Splunk, ELK, or Graylog with reporting features
   - Create custom audit report scripts using XO REST API:
     curl -sk -H "Authorization: Bearer TOKEN" https://xo/rest/v0/plugins/audit/records
2. Define organizational reporting requirements:
   - Frequency: daily summary, weekly trend, monthly compliance
   - Scope: all users, privileged users only, specific event types
   - Format: CSV, JSON, PDF for management review
3. Automate report distribution to ISSO, SA, and management
4. Implement compliance reporting tied to STIG requirements
5. Document reporting schedule and distribution list in SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides report generation capability supporting on-demand reporting requirements.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized solution can generate on-demand reports
2. Verify report content covers organization-defined reporting requirements
3. Confirm reports are accessible to ISSO and SA without special access
4. Document report generation procedures and schedule in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222494">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No report generation capability was detected that supports after-the-fact security incident investigations. Without a dedicated forensic reporting tool, investigating security incidents requires manual log analysis.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Implement forensic report generation capability:
   - SIEM correlation rules for incident reconstruction
   - Log analysis scripts that can reconstruct event timelines
   - Audit record export in forensically sound formats
2. Create incident investigation report templates:
   - Timeline reconstruction report
   - User activity trace report
   - Access pattern anomaly report
3. Configure long-term log retention for forensic availability:
   - Minimum 1 year online/accessible retention
   - Archive to write-once media for chain of custody
4. Train SA and ISSO on generating forensic reports
5. Document forensic reporting procedures in Incident Response Plan

LEGAL CONSIDERATION: Ensure forensic report generation meets requirements for potential legal proceedings (chain of custody, integrity verification).</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides report generation capability supporting after-the-fact security incident investigations.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized solution supports forensic-quality report generation
2. Verify audit records are preserved with integrity for investigation use
3. Confirm reports can span the full incident timeline across all XO components
4. Document the forensic investigation and reporting procedures in the IRP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222495">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No audit reduction capability was detected that preserves original audit record content and time ordering. Manual log review of XO logs is susceptible to accidental modification without protective controls.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Protect original log files from modification:
   chattr +a /var/log/xo-server/  # append-only
   chattr +i /var/log/xo-server/archived-logs/  # immutable after archival
2. Configure audit reduction to use read-only access to source logs:
   - Mount log directory read-only for analysis: mount --bind -o ro /var/log/xo-server /mnt/ro-logs
   - Use log shipping to separate analysis system
3. Implement integrity verification:
   - Compute checksums of original logs before analysis: sha256sum /var/log/xo-server/*
   - Store checksums in a separate tamper-evident location
4. Configure SIEM to ingest logs as read-only copies
5. Document the audit reduction integrity preservation procedure in the SSP

CRITICAL: Audit reduction tools must never modify timestamps or reorder events in source audit records.</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides audit reduction without altering original audit record content or time ordering.

Per ASD STIG check content: if the application uses a centralized logging mechanism provided by the platform, this requirement is Not Applicable.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the centralized solution maintains original record integrity during reduction
2. Verify the SIEM/log management solution does not modify timestamps or reorder events
3. Confirm source log integrity is preserved (checksums, append-only storage)
4. Document the audit reduction integrity controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222496">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>This requirement is Not Applicable. A centralized logging solution is configured that provides report generation preserving original audit record content and time ordering.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the SIEM generates reports without modifying source audit records
2. Verify reports maintain chronological ordering of events
3. Document the centralized report generation capability in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No centralized logging solution was detected that provides report generation preserving original content and time ordering.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Deploy a centralized SIEM (Splunk, ELK, Graylog) with report generation
2. Verify report generation does not alter source audit records
3. Configure read-only access to source logs during report generation
4. Document the report generation integrity controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222497">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>The system uses internal system clocks synchronized via NTP/chrony/timesyncd for generating audit record timestamps. XO (Node.js) uses the system clock (Date.now()) for all timestamp generation.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm NTP synchronization is active and configured to DoD time sources
2. Verify XO audit plugin timestamps align with system clock
3. Document the NTP configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No active NTP synchronization was detected. The system clock may not be reliable for audit timestamp generation.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Install and configure chrony or ntp:
   apt install chrony
   systemctl enable --now chronyd
2. Configure DoD-approved NTP sources in /etc/chrony/chrony.conf
3. Verify synchronization: chronyc sources
4. Document NTP configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222498">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit timestamps can be mapped to UTC. The system timezone offset is known, systemd journal natively supports UTC output, and Node.js Date objects store time internally as UTC milliseconds.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm timezone is configured correctly (timedatectl)
2. Verify log timestamps include timezone offset or are in UTC
3. For UTC-only requirement, configure: timedatectl set-timezone UTC</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit timestamps cannot be reliably mapped to UTC. The system timezone configuration may be incorrect or log timestamps lack timezone information.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Set the system timezone to UTC for DoD compliance:
   timedatectl set-timezone UTC
2. Configure XO to use UTC timestamps in logging
3. Verify journal output with: journalctl --output=short-iso
4. Document the timezone configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222499">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit timestamps exceed the minimum 1-second granularity requirement. Systemd journal provides microsecond precision. XO audit plugin records timestamps as Unix milliseconds (Date.now()).

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify journal timestamp precision: journalctl --output=short-precise
2. Confirm XO audit records contain millisecond timestamps
3. Document the timestamp precision in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit timestamps do not meet the minimum 1-second granularity requirement.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Verify systemd journal is configured for persistent storage
2. Check XO logging configuration for timestamp format
3. Ensure Node.js Date.now() is used (not truncated to seconds)
4. Document the timestamp granularity in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222500">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit information is protected from unauthorized read access. Log directories are owned by root with restricted permissions. Systemd journal access is controlled by the systemd-journal group membership.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify log directory permissions: stat /var/log/xo-server /var/log/journal
2. Confirm no world-readable log files exist
3. Review systemd-journal group membership for authorized users only</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit information may be accessible to unauthorized readers. World-readable log files or overly permissive directory permissions were detected.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Fix log directory permissions:
   chmod 750 /var/log/xo-server
   chown root:adm /var/log/xo-server
2. Fix individual log file permissions:
   chmod 640 /var/log/xo-server/*.log
3. Review and restrict systemd-journal group membership
4. Document the access control configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222501">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit information is protected from unauthorized modification. Log files are owned by root with no world-write permissions. Systemd journal uses a binary format with built-in integrity checking.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify no world-writable log files exist
2. Confirm log directory ownership is root
3. Consider enabling append-only attributes: chattr +a /var/log/xo-server/</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit information may be modifiable by unauthorized users. World-writable log files or insufficient directory permissions were detected.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Remove world-write permissions:
   chmod -R o-w /var/log/xo-server/
2. Set append-only attribute: chattr +a /var/log/xo-server/*.log
3. Configure logrotate to maintain proper permissions on rotated files
4. Document the modification protection controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222502">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit information is protected from unauthorized deletion. Log directories are owned by root with restricted permissions. Only root can delete log files.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify log directory ownership: ls -la /var/log/xo-server/
2. Confirm only root has delete permissions on log files
3. Consider setting immutable attributes on archived logs</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit information may be deletable by unauthorized users.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Restrict log directory permissions:
   chmod 750 /var/log/xo-server
   chown root:adm /var/log/xo-server
2. Set immutable attribute on archived logs: chattr +i /var/log/xo-server/archived/
3. Forward logs to a centralized SIEM for off-system preservation
4. Document the deletion protection controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222503">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit tools are protected from unauthorized access. System audit tools (journalctl, logger, aureport, ausearch) are owned by root with standard permissions managed by the dpkg package manager.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify audit tool permissions: stat /usr/bin/journalctl /usr/sbin/aureport
2. Confirm tools are owned by root
3. Document the audit tool access controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Some audit tools may have overly permissive access settings.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Reset audit tool permissions to package defaults:
   apt install --reinstall coreutils systemd
2. Verify permissions after reset: dpkg --verify coreutils systemd
3. Restrict access to sensitive audit tools (aureport, ausearch)
4. Document the remediation in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222504">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit tools are protected from unauthorized modification. System audit tools are managed by the dpkg package manager which maintains cryptographic hashes. Only root can modify files in /usr/bin and /usr/sbin.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify package integrity: dpkg --verify coreutils systemd
2. Confirm no group/other write permissions on audit tools
3. Document the modification protection controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Some audit tools may be modifiable by non-root users.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Remove group/other write permissions:
   chmod go-w /usr/bin/journalctl /usr/sbin/aureport /usr/sbin/ausearch
2. Verify package integrity: dpkg --verify coreutils systemd
3. Install AIDE for ongoing integrity monitoring: apt install aide
4. Document the remediation in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222505">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit tools are protected from unauthorized deletion. Tool directories (/usr/bin, /usr/sbin) are owned by root and not world-writable. Package management (dpkg/apt) requires root for removal.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify directory permissions: stat /usr/bin /usr/sbin
2. Confirm only root can remove packages: apt requires sudo
3. Document the deletion protection controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit tool directories may allow unauthorized deletion.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Fix directory permissions:
   chmod 755 /usr/bin /usr/sbin
   chown root:root /usr/bin /usr/sbin
2. Verify no unauthorized users have sudo access to apt/dpkg
3. Consider immutable attributes on critical audit tools
4. Document the remediation in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222506">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit records are backed up via centralized logging which forwards logs in real-time, exceeding the 7-day backup requirement.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm centralized logging is actively forwarding all XO audit records
2. Verify the centralized system retains logs per organizational policy
3. Confirm backup frequency exceeds the 7-day minimum requirement
4. Document the audit record backup configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No verified backup mechanism for audit records to a separate system. Local logrotate provides archival but not off-system backup.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Configure rsyslog to forward logs to centralized syslog server:
   Add to /etc/rsyslog.conf: *.* @@siem-server:514
2. Alternatively, configure scheduled backup:
   cron job: 0 0 * * 0 rsync -a /var/log/xo-server/ backup-server:/backup/xo-logs/
3. Configure systemd-journal-remote for journal forwarding
4. Verify backup occurs at minimum every 7 days
5. Document the backup configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222507">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Cryptographic mechanisms are in use to protect audit information integrity. This may include systemd journal Forward Secure Sealing (FSS), AIDE file integrity monitoring, or TLS-protected log transmission.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm the cryptographic integrity mechanism is active and configured
2. Verify audit records cannot be modified without detection
3. Document the integrity protection mechanism in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No cryptographic integrity protection detected for audit records.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Enable systemd journal Forward Secure Sealing:
   Set Seal=yes in /etc/systemd/journald.conf
   systemctl restart systemd-journald
2. Install AIDE for file integrity monitoring:
   apt install aide
   aideinit
3. Configure TLS for remote log transmission (rsyslog with TLS)
4. Document the integrity protection in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222508">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit tools are cryptographically hashed through the dpkg package management system, which maintains MD5 checksums for all installed package files. dpkg --verify validates current file state against stored checksums.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Run dpkg --verify for audit tool packages
2. Verify no unauthorized modifications are reported
3. Document the package integrity verification in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit tool cryptographic hashing verification has failed or is not available.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Verify dpkg integrity checking is functional: dpkg --verify coreutils systemd
2. Reinstall modified packages: apt install --reinstall [package]
3. Install debsums for additional integrity checking: apt install debsums
4. Document the remediation in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222509">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Audit tool integrity is validated through cryptographic hash checking. Mechanisms may include AIDE scheduled checks, debsums verification, dpkg --verify, or journalctl --verify.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm integrity checking is scheduled (cron/systemd timer)
2. Verify the checking mechanism runs at organization-defined frequency
3. Document the integrity validation schedule in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No automated audit tool integrity validation mechanism was detected.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Install AIDE: apt install aide &amp;&amp; aideinit
2. Configure daily AIDE check: add to /etc/cron.daily/aide
3. Install debsums: apt install debsums
4. Configure scheduled integrity validation
5. Document the validation schedule and procedures in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222510">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Software installation requires privileged (root/sudo) access. The apt/dpkg package managers enforce root-level permissions for software installation, modification, and removal by default on Debian 12.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm apt/dpkg require root or sudo for installation
2. Review sudo configuration for authorized software installers
3. Document the software installation policy in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Non-privileged users may be able to install software.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Review sudo configuration: visudo
2. Remove unnecessary sudo permissions for package management
3. Restrict polkit policies for package installation
4. Document the software installation restrictions in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222511">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Access restrictions are enforced for configuration changes. XO RBAC requires admin role for configuration modifications. Config files are root-owned with restricted permissions.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify XO admin role is required for configuration changes
2. Confirm config file permissions are restricted (600 or 640)
3. Document the configuration change access controls in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Configuration files may be modifiable by non-privileged users.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Fix config file permissions:
   chmod 600 /etc/xo-server/config.toml
   chown root:root /etc/xo-server/config.toml
2. Verify XO RBAC is enforced (admin role required for settings)
3. Restrict systemd service file permissions
4. Document the access restriction configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222512">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Configuration changes are audited with user attribution. The XO audit plugin records all administrative actions including configuration changes with user identity and timestamp. Systemd journal records service configuration events.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify the XO audit plugin is enabled and recording events
2. Confirm configuration change events include user identity
3. Document the configuration auditing capability in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>No configuration change auditing mechanism was detected.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Enable the XO audit plugin in Settings &gt; Plugins
2. Configure auditd rules for XO config files:
   auditctl -w /etc/xo-server/config.toml -p wa -k xo-config
3. Verify auditing captures user identity for all config changes
4. Document the auditing configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222513">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Software component installation requires digital signature verification. APT enforces GPG signature verification by default. npm uses SHA-512 integrity hashes in package-lock.json.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm APT signature verification is not disabled
2. Verify GPG keys are from trusted sources
3. Confirm npm integrity checking is enabled (package-lock)
4. Document the signature verification configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Unsigned package installation may be allowed or signature verification is disabled.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Remove any AllowUnauthenticated settings from APT config:
   grep -r AllowUnauthenticated /etc/apt/
2. Verify GPG keys: apt-key list
3. Enable npm package-lock: npm config set package-lock true
4. Document the signature verification configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222514">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Software library directories are protected with appropriate permissions. Only privileged users can modify library contents. XO node_modules, system libraries, and npm global packages are root-owned.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify no world-writable files in /opt/xo/ or /usr/lib/
2. Confirm library directories are root-owned
3. Document the library protection configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Some software libraries may be modifiable by non-privileged users.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Fix permissions on XO libraries:
   chown -R root:root /opt/xo/node_modules
   chmod -R o-w /opt/xo/
2. Fix system library permissions:
   chmod -R o-w /usr/lib/ /usr/local/lib/
3. Verify npm global directory permissions
4. Document the library protection in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222515">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>An application vulnerability assessment program is in place. This includes STIG compliance scanning via Evaluate-STIG, npm security audits, and Debian security update monitoring.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm regular vulnerability assessments are conducted
2. Verify assessment scope covers all application components
3. Document the assessment program in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Vulnerability assessment evidence is limited. A comprehensive vulnerability assessment program must be documented.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Establish a vulnerability assessment program:
   - Define scope (XO application, OS, dependencies)
   - Define frequency (quarterly minimum)
   - Assign responsible personnel
2. Run regular npm audits: npm audit
3. Monitor Debian security updates: apt list --upgradable
4. Schedule STIG compliance scans with Evaluate-STIG
5. Document the assessment program in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222516">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Program execution control mechanisms are in place including AppArmor profiles, systemd service management, XO plugin control, and noexec mount options.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm organization-defined execution policies are documented
2. Verify AppArmor enforcement mode for applicable profiles
3. Document the execution control configuration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Program execution control mechanisms exist but organization-defined execution policies must be documented and verified.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Document organization-defined software execution policies
2. Enable AppArmor enforcement for XO-related profiles
3. Disable unnecessary services: systemctl disable [service]
4. Configure noexec on /tmp and /var/tmp mount points
5. Document the execution control policies in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222517">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>A deny-all, permit-by-exception approach is implemented through XO RBAC, AppArmor profiles, and firewall rules. XO enforces role-based access where non-permitted actions are denied by default.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm XO RBAC is configured with least-privilege roles
2. Verify AppArmor or similar application control is enforcing
3. Document the whitelist/exception-based policy in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Organization-defined software execution policies using deny-all, permit-by- exception approach must be documented and verified.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Document the authorized software whitelist
2. Configure AppArmor profiles for XO components
3. Implement firewall deny-all with specific allow rules
4. Configure XO RBAC with minimum necessary permissions
5. Document the deny-all, permit-by-exception policy in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222518">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Non-essential capabilities have been reviewed and disabled. Only mission- essential services, plugins, and features are enabled.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Review enabled services and confirm all are mission-essential
2. Review XO plugins and confirm all are required
3. Confirm no debug/development features are enabled in production
4. Document the capability review in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Non-essential capability review requires organizational determination of which plugins, services, and features are mission-essential.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Review and document mission-essential services
2. Disable unnecessary XO plugins in Settings &gt; Plugins
3. Disable non-essential system services: systemctl disable [service]
4. Ensure Node.js debug mode is disabled (no --inspect flags)
5. Document the capability review and disabled items in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222519">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>All ports/protocols in use are registered in the PPSM CAL and only authorized functions are enabled. Firewall rules restrict to approved ports only.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Verify all listening ports are registered in the PPSM CAL
2. Confirm firewall rules match PPSM CAL approved ports
3. Document the PPSM CAL registration in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Listening ports have been enumerated. Organization must verify all ports/ protocols are registered in the PPSM CAL.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Document all required ports/protocols:
   TCP 443 (HTTPS), TCP 22 (SSH), TCP 80 (HTTP redirect)
2. Register all ports in the PPSM CAL
3. Configure firewall to allow only PPSM-approved ports
4. Disable any services using unregistered ports
5. Document the PPSM CAL compliance in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222520">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>User reauthentication is required for organization-defined circumstances including session timeout, privilege escalation, and authentication factor changes.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm reauthentication triggers are documented
2. Verify session timeout forces re-login
3. Document the reauthentication policy in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Reauthentication mechanisms exist but organization-defined circumstances requiring reauthentication must be documented.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Document organization-defined reauthentication circumstances:
   - Session timeout (idle and absolute)
   - Privilege escalation (role change)
   - Authentication factor changes
2. Configure XO session timeout in config.toml
3. Configure sudo timeout: Defaults timestamp_timeout=5
4. Document the reauthentication policy in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222521">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Device reauthentication mechanisms are in place including SSH host key verification, TLS certificate authentication, and XCP-ng host connection management requiring reauthentication on reconnection.

ISSO VERIFICATION:
1. Confirm device reauthentication triggers are documented
2. Verify TLS certificate validation on device connections
3. Document the device reauthentication policy in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus>
        <ValidTrueComment>Device authentication mechanisms exist (SSH host keys, TLS certificates) but organization-defined circumstances requiring device reauthentication must be documented.

REMEDIATION STEPS:
1. Document organization-defined device reauthentication circumstances:
   - Network reconnection
   - Certificate expiration/renewal
   - Security posture changes
2. Configure XO to validate XCP-ng host certificates
3. Enable SSH host key verification: StrictHostKeyChecking yes
4. Document the device reauthentication policy in the SSP</ValidTrueComment>
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222522">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222523">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra privileged account access has been verified for MFA/Alt Token compliance.

Enterprise authentication integration (LDAP/AD with smart card or SAML with MFA-enabled IdP) is configured, providing multifactor authentication for privileged network access to the XO management console.

Evidence examined:
- Authentication plugin configuration (auth-ldap or auth-saml)
- TLS client certificate settings
- Privileged user account enumeration via REST API

The organization has implemented MFA through directory services integration, meeting DoD requirements for privileged network access authentication.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra does not natively enforce multifactor authentication for privileged network access.

Current state: XO uses local username/password authentication by default. No MFA/Alt Token enforcement detected for admin accounts.

Remediation actions:
1. Configure LDAP/AD integration with smart card (CAC/PIV) authentication
2. Or configure SAML/OIDC integration with MFA-enabled Identity Provider
3. Ensure all admin accounts require MFA before network access
4. Document MFA enforcement in the system security plan

Reference: VATES_COMPLIANCE_BLOCKERS.md - MFA/2FA not built into XO</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222524">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>PIV credential acceptance has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

The system is configured to accept PIV credentials through TLS client certificate authentication or LDAP/AD integration with smart card support. PKCS#11 packages are installed on the host system.

Evidence examined:
- TLS client certificate configuration
- PKCS#11/smart card package installation
- Authentication plugin configuration</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Xen Orchestra does not natively accept PIV credentials.

Current state: XO uses local username/password or token-based authentication. No PIV/CAC credential acceptance configured.

Remediation actions:
1. Install PKCS#11 packages (opensc, p11-kit, pam-pkcs11)
2. Configure TLS client certificate authentication in XO
3. Or integrate with LDAP/AD that supports smart card authentication
4. Test PIV credential acceptance with DoD CAC cards</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222525">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>PIV credential electronic verification has been confirmed for Xen Orchestra.

The system validates PIV credentials through OCSP/CRL certificate revocation checking and TLS client certificate verification.

Evidence examined:
- OCSP/CRL revocation checking configuration
- TLS client certificate verification settings
- Certificate chain validation</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>PIV credential electronic verification is not configured for Xen Orchestra.

Current state: No OCSP or CRL revocation checking configured for client certificates. Certificate chain validation is limited to server-side TLS.

Remediation actions:
1. Configure OCSP stapling or CRL distribution point checking
2. Enable TLS client certificate verification with revocation checking
3. Configure certificate chain validation against DoD PKI trust anchors
4. Test credential verification with revoked certificates</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222526">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>MFA for non-privileged network access has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

Enterprise authentication (LDAP/AD or SAML) with MFA capability is configured for all user accounts, including non-privileged users.

Evidence examined:
- Authentication plugin configuration
- Non-privileged user account enumeration
- MFA enforcement settings</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>MFA is not enforced for non-privileged network access to Xen Orchestra.

Current state: Non-privileged users authenticate with username/password only. No MFA enforcement for standard user accounts.

Remediation actions:
1. Configure LDAP/AD integration with CAC/PIV for all users
2. Or configure SAML/OIDC with MFA-enabled IdP
3. Ensure MFA applies to both privileged and non-privileged accounts
4. Document MFA enforcement in access control policy</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222527">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>MFA for local privileged access has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

PAM MFA modules or SSH multi-factor authentication is configured for local privileged access to the XO server.

Evidence examined:
- PAM configuration (pam_pkcs11, pam_u2f, pam_google_authenticator)
- SSH AuthenticationMethods configuration
- Local console access controls</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>MFA is not enforced for local privileged access to the Xen Orchestra server.

Current state: Local access uses standard password authentication without additional factors.

Remediation actions:
1. Configure PAM MFA module (pam_pkcs11 for smart card, pam_u2f for FIDO2)
2. Configure SSH AuthenticationMethods to require publickey and password
3. Restrict local console access to authorized administrators
4. Document local access MFA requirements</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222528">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>MFA for local nonprivileged access has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

PAM MFA modules or SAML integration provides multifactor authentication for all local user access.

Evidence examined:
- PAM MFA configuration
- SAML/OIDC authentication settings
- Web interface authentication methods</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>MFA is not enforced for local nonprivileged access to Xen Orchestra.

Current state: Local nonprivileged users authenticate with username/password only.

Remediation actions:
1. Configure PAM MFA module for system-level authentication
2. Configure SAML/OIDC with MFA-enabled IdP for web access
3. Ensure MFA applies to all user types
4. Document authentication requirements for nonprivileged users</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222529">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Individual authentication before group access has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

All XO user accounts use individual email/username credentials. No shared or group accounts were detected in the XO user database. Each user must authenticate individually before accessing any shared resources.

Evidence examined:
- XO user account listing via REST API
- Shared/group account detection
- Recent login activity analysis</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Individual authentication before group access requires verification for Xen Orchestra.

Current state: Possible shared or group accounts detected in XO user database. Individual authentication before shared access must be verified.

Remediation actions:
1. Review all XO user accounts for shared/generic credentials
2. Convert shared accounts to individual accounts
3. If shared accounts are required, implement individual login first
4. Document shared account usage and individual authentication procedures</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222530">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Replay-resistant authentication for privileged access has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

XO uses session-based authentication over TLS 1.2+. TLS encryption prevents credential interception and replay. Session tokens are unique per session and time-limited.

Evidence examined:
- TLS version and cipher configuration
- Session token management
- CSRF protection headers</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Replay-resistant authentication for privileged access cannot be fully verified.

Current state: TLS configuration may not fully prevent replay attacks.

Remediation actions:
1. Ensure TLS 1.2+ is the minimum supported version
2. Verify session tokens are cryptographically random and time-limited
3. Enable CSRF protection tokens
4. Disable TLS session resumption if replay is a concern</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222531">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Replay-resistant authentication for nonprivileged access has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

The same TLS 1.2+ session-based authentication mechanism applies to all user accounts (both privileged and nonprivileged), providing replay protection through encrypted transport and unique session tokens.

Evidence examined:
- TLS encryption active for all connections
- Uniform authentication mechanism for all users</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Replay-resistant authentication for nonprivileged access cannot be fully verified.

Remediation: Ensure TLS 1.2+ is enforced for all connections. Verify session tokens are cryptographically random and time-limited for all user accounts.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222532">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Mutual authentication for non-repudiation has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

Mutual TLS (mTLS) is configured, providing both server and client certificate verification. This ensures device-level non-repudiation for management operations.

Evidence examined:
- TLS client certificate configuration
- Server certificate verification
- Mutual authentication settings</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Mutual authentication (mTLS) is not configured for Xen Orchestra.

Current state: Server-side TLS only. No client certificate authentication configured.

Remediation actions:
1. Configure TLS client certificate requirements in XO config
2. Deploy client certificates to authorized management endpoints
3. Configure certificate chain validation against DoD PKI
4. Document mutual authentication requirements and implementation</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222533">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Endpoint device authentication has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

The XO API correctly rejects unauthenticated requests (HTTP 401/403). All management operations require authentication tokens. HTTP traffic is redirected to HTTPS.

Evidence examined:
- Unauthenticated API access test (401/403 response)
- HTTP to HTTPS redirect verification
- WebSocket authentication requirements</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Endpoint device authentication requires verification for Xen Orchestra.

Remediation actions:
1. Verify all API endpoints require authentication tokens
2. Ensure HTTP redirects to HTTPS for all connections
3. Verify WebSocket connections require valid session tokens
4. Implement network access controls to limit endpoint connections</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222534">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Mutual SSL/TLS for service-oriented access has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

XO REST API endpoints use TLS with client certificate authentication for service consumers handling non-releasable virtualization management data.

Evidence examined:
- REST API TLS configuration
- Client certificate requirements
- Data classification assessment</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Mutual SSL/TLS is not configured for XO service-oriented endpoints.

Current state: REST API uses token-based authentication over server-side TLS. No client certificate requirements for API consumers.

Remediation actions:
1. Configure TLS client certificate requirements for REST API
2. Deploy client certificates to authorized service consumers
3. Document data classification and mutual TLS requirements
4. Test mTLS with API consumers</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222535">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Device identifier management has been assessed for Xen Orchestra. XO authenticates users, not devices, making this requirement Not Applicable per STIG guidance.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Device identifier inactivity management requires review.

Remediation: If XO is configured to authenticate devices, ensure device identifiers are disabled after 35 days of inactivity. If using DoD PKI certificates for device authentication, the expiration date on the certificate fulfills this requirement.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="3" ExpectedStatus="Not_Applicable">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Not_Applicable</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Not Applicable. Xen Orchestra is a web-based management application that authenticates users, not devices. XO does not use device identifiers for authentication.

Per STIG guidance: "If the application is not designed to authenticate devices, this is Not Applicable."

User authentication is managed through individual user accounts with email/username credentials. Browser sessions are authenticated via user credentials, not device identifiers.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222536">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222537">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password uppercase requirement has been verified for Xen Orchestra.

PAM pwquality module is configured with ucredit = -1 (or stricter), requiring at least one uppercase character in passwords.

Evidence examined:
- /etc/security/pwquality.conf ucredit setting
- PAM module configuration
- External authentication delegation (LDAP/AD)</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password uppercase requirement is not enforced for Xen Orchestra.

Current state: PAM pwquality ucredit not configured to require uppercase characters.

Remediation actions:
1. Set ucredit = -1 in /etc/security/pwquality.conf
2. Ensure pam_pwquality is loaded in PAM stack (/etc/pam.d/common-password)
3. If using LDAP/AD, verify directory password policy enforces uppercase
4. Test password change with all-lowercase password (should be rejected)</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222538">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password lowercase requirement has been verified. PAM pwquality lcredit = -1 configured.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password lowercase requirement is not enforced.

Remediation: Set lcredit = -1 in /etc/security/pwquality.conf. Ensure pam_pwquality is loaded in PAM stack. If using LDAP/AD, verify directory password policy enforces lowercase.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222539">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password numeric requirement has been verified. PAM pwquality dcredit = -1 configured.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password numeric character requirement is not enforced.

Remediation: Set dcredit = -1 in /etc/security/pwquality.conf. Ensure pam_pwquality is loaded in PAM stack. If using LDAP/AD, verify directory password policy enforces numeric characters.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222540">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password special character requirement has been verified. PAM pwquality ocredit = -1 configured.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password special character requirement is not enforced.

Remediation: Set ocredit = -1 in /etc/security/pwquality.conf. Ensure pam_pwquality is loaded in PAM stack. If using LDAP/AD, verify directory password policy enforces special characters.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222541">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password change difference requirement has been verified. PAM pwquality difok = 8 (or higher) configured, requiring at least 8 characters differ from old password.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Password change difference requirement is not enforced.

Current state: PAM pwquality difok not configured to require 8+ character changes (default is 1).

Remediation: Set difok = 8 in /etc/security/pwquality.conf. Ensure pam_pwquality is loaded in PAM stack.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222542">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222543">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222544">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Minimum password lifetime of 24 hours has been verified. PASS_MIN_DAYS is set to 1 or greater in /etc/login.defs.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Minimum password lifetime is not enforced.

Current state: PASS_MIN_DAYS not configured or set to 0 in /etc/login.defs.

Remediation: Set PASS_MIN_DAYS 1 in /etc/login.defs. Apply to existing users with: chage --mindays 1 username. If using LDAP/AD, verify directory enforces minimum password age.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222545">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="NotAFinding">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>NotAFinding</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Maximum password lifetime of 60 days has been verified. PASS_MAX_DAYS is set to 60 or less in /etc/login.defs.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
      <Answer Index="2" ExpectedStatus="Open">
        <ValidationCode /><ValidTrueStatus>Open</ValidTrueStatus><ValidTrueComment>Maximum password lifetime is not properly configured.

Current state: PASS_MAX_DAYS not set to 60 or less in /etc/login.defs.

Remediation: Set PASS_MAX_DAYS 60 in /etc/login.defs. Apply to existing users with: chage --maxdays 60 username. If using LDAP/AD, verify directory enforces maximum password age of 60 days.</ValidTrueComment><ValidFalseStatus /><ValidFalseComment /></Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222546">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222547">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222548">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222549">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222550">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222551">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222552">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222553">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222554">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222555">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222556">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222557">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222558">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222559">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222560">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222561">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222562">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222563">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222564">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222565">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222566">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222567">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222568">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222570">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222571">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222572">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222573">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222574">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222575">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222576">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222577">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222578">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222579">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222580">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222581">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222582">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222583">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222584">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222585">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222586">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222587">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222588">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222589">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222590">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222591">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222592">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222593">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222594">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222595">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222596">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222597">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222598">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222599">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222600">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222601">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222602">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222603">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222604">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222605">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222606">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222607">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222608">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222609">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222610">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222611">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222612">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222613">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222614">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222615">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222616">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222617">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222618">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222619">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222620">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222621">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222622">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222623">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222624">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222625">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222626">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222627">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222628">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222629">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222630">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222631">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222632">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222633">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222634">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222635">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222636">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222637">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222638">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222639">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222640">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222641">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222642">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222643">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222644">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222645">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222646">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222647">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222648">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222649">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222650">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222651">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222652">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222653">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222654">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222655">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222656">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222657">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222658">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222659">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222660">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222661">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222662">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222663">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222664">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222665">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222666">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222667">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222668">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222669">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222670">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222671">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222672">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-222673">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
  <Vuln ID="V-265634">
    
    <AnswerKey Name="XO">
      
      <Answer Index="1" ExpectedStatus="Not_Reviewed" Hostname="" Instance="" Database="" Site="" ResultHash="">
        
        <ValidationCode />
        <ValidTrueStatus />
        <ValidTrueComment />
        <ValidFalseStatus />
        <ValidFalseComment />
      </Answer>
    </AnswerKey>
  </Vuln>
</STIGComments>